<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE tmx SYSTEM "tmx11.dtd">
<tmx version="1.1">
  <header creationtool="OmegaT" o-tmf="OmegaT TMX" adminlang="EN-US" datatype="plaintext" creationtoolversion="4.1.5_4_10550" segtype="sentence" srclang="EN-US"/>
  <body>
<!-- Default translations -->
<!-- Alternative translations -->
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\noindent</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.8em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>1.\quad  Similar to file download, multiple virtual connections (tunnels) are established with each peer, and the estimated transmission speed $V_{conn}$ is calculated per virtual connection.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T112519Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T112519Z">
        <seg>1.\quad  Аналогично скачиванию файлов, с каждым пиром устанавливается несколько виртуальных соединений (туннелей) и оценивается скорость передачи $V_{conn}$ на каждое виртуальное соединение.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\noindent</prop>
      <prop type="next">UDP based protocols such as KCP or UDT\cite{article13} are attempted first to make the connection.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>1.\quad Multiple virtual connections (Tunnels) are established between the user and each peer with the resources, to improve transmission efficiency.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T094717Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T094516Z">
        <seg>1.\quad Для увеличения эффективности передачи, между пользователем и каждым пиром, обладающим нужными данными, устанавливаются несколько виртуальных соединений (Туннелей).</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\noindent</prop>
      <prop type="next">If no history is found, a default empirical value is used.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>2.\quad For each peer, an expected download speed $V_{conn}$ is calculated based on its transmission history.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T095229Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T095229Z">
        <seg>2.\quad Для каждого пира, на основе его истории передачи вычисляется скорость скачивания $V_{conn}$.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\noindent</prop>
      <prop type="next">The estimated arrival time for each piece can be calculated based on the speed of each virtual connection and the remaining pieces to be downloaded in each queue.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>2.\quad Pieces to be downloaded are sorted based on their priorities and pre-allocated to available virtual connections by placing them in the corresponding download queues.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T113418Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T112828Z">
        <seg>2.\quad Части к загрузке сортируются на основе их приоритетов и предварительно распределяются по имеющимся виртуальным соединениям, размещаются в соответствующих очередях на скачивание.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\noindent</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.8em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>3.\quad Step 2 is repeated periodically, and all remaining pieces will be re-allocated to accommodate changes in the transmission speed and availability of the virtual connections.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T132405Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T132405Z">
        <seg>3.\quad Шаг 2 повторяется циклически, все оставшиеся части будут пере-распределены в соответствии с изменениями скорости передачи и доступности виртуальных соединений.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\noindent</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.8em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>3.\quad The number of virtual connections on each peer varies the peer with a higher $V_{conn}$ can have a significant number of initial virtual connections.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T095625Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T095625Z">
        <seg>3.\quad Количество виртуальных соединений с каждым пиром различно, пир с высоким $V_{conn}$ может иметь значительное число виртуальных соединений изначально.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\noindent</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.8em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>4.\quad After a piece is successfully downloaded, the transmission speed of the virtual connection is updated, and a request is sent immediately to download the next piece in the queue.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T132538Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T132538Z">
        <seg>4.\quad После успешной загрузки части обновляется оценка скорости передачи виртуального соединения, сразу же отсылается запрос на скачивание следующей части в очереди.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\noindent</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.8em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>4.\quad Based on the partition of the segment, the user first sends a download request to a given peer for an arbitrary piece, and the peer responds accordingly by sending the user the piece upon receiving the request.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T100057Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T100057Z">
        <seg>4.\quad На основании разбиения сегмента пользователь сначала шлет пиру запрос на скачивание какой то конкретной части, при получении запроса пир отвечает пользователю отсылкой соответствующей части.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\noindent</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.8em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>5.\quad  Urgent pieces can be requested from multiple connections to ensure smooth playback.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T132723Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T132723Z">
        <seg>5.\quad  Для более мягкого воспроизведения, наиболее востребованные части могут быть запрошены сквозь несколько соединений.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\noindent</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.8em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>5.\quad When a piece is received from a virtual connection, the estimated download speed $V_{conn}$ is updated, and another remaining arbitrary piece will be requested from the connection immediately until all the data is downloaded.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T100502Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T100502Z">
        <seg>5.\quad При получении из виртуального соединения запрошенной части производится обновление оценочной скорости скачивания $V_{conn}$, далее немедленно запрашивается какая то другая часть, до тех пор, пока не будут скачаны все данные.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\noindent</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.5em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>6.\quad  Other parts of the algorithm work the same way as in regular file download.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T132817Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T132817Z">
        <seg>6.\quad  В остальном алгоритм работает так же как и в случае обычного скачивания файлов.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\noindent</prop>
      <prop type="next">The download requests of the remaining pieces will be re-routed to other peers.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>6.\quad When a download request times out, the request is canceled, and all connections to the non-responding peer will be closed.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T100737Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T100737Z">
        <seg>6.\quad В случае истечения времени ожидания ответа соответствующий запрос на скачивание отменяется, все соединения к не-отвечающему пиру закрываются.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\\ \\When user uploads data to PPIO's storage network, its neighbors with a closer network distance are prioritized when selecting storage miners to store the data.</prop>
      <prop type="next">When enough miner nodes join the network in different regions of the world, high data transfer speed can be maintained around the globe.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>A large percentage of the copies of the data are stored on the neighboring miners with a faster connection to the user, to achieve higher transfer speed during storage and retrieval.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190320T115034Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190320T115034Z">
        <seg>Для достижения более высокой скорости сохранения и получения данных, большой процент копий этих данных сохраняется на соседних майнерах с более быстрым соединением с пользователем.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">Each of these N miners is also called a “Peer”.</prop>
      <prop type="next">This process is called {\bf Multi-point Download Scheduling}.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>A scheduler decides how the M pieces can be downloaded from the N peers so that the segment can be retrieved in a fast, efficient manner, and avoid duplicated pieces to be downloaded.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T093720Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T093720Z">
        <seg>Планировщик решает, как M частей могут быть получены от N пиров так чтобы весь сегмент мог быть получен быстро и эффективно, с недопущением пересылки дублируемых частей.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">The scheduler is also designed to maximize download speed and minimize the overhead of duplicated requests and data transmission.</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.8em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>A summary of the scheduling algorithm is as follows:</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T112318Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T112318Z">
        <seg>Далее приводится краткая сводка представленного алгоритма планирования:</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">In general, pieces with higher priority should end up with an earlier estimated arrival time.</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.8em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>An illustration of the pre-allocation algorithm is shown in Figure 2.1.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T113735Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T113657Z">
        <seg>На Рисунке 2.1 показан пример действия алгоритма предварительного распределения.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">Light Proof of Capacity (LPoC) is developed to provide lightweight validation of storage capacity provided by the miners.</prop>
      <prop type="next">Proof of Replication (PoRep) is used to guarantee that the miners replicate user's data.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>An optimized Proof of Space-Time (PoSt) ensures that the specified data is indeed stored by the miner over a period.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190314T163940Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190314T163940Z">
        <seg>Оптимизированное доказательство хранения с течением времени (Оptimized Proof of Space-Time, PoSt) убеждает что заданные данные действительно сохранены майнером в течении периода времени.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">It also adapts to the popularity of data in different regions.</prop>
      <prop type="next">Miners in other parts of the network are not affected.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>As PPIO’s overlay network is built by clustering nearby peers, if a piece of content is only popular in a certain region, only the miners in the same region populate it extensively.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190325T150051Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190325T150051Z">
        <seg>Оверлейная сеть PPIO строится в виде кластеров расположенных рядом пиров, и если какая то часть данных популярна в заданном регионе, то их широкое распространение будут производить только майнеры из этого же региона.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">Such deficiency in the design can lead to many real-world problems to the miners and ISPs.</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.5em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>As Protocol Labs claims that files stored on IPFS are permanent and cannot be deleted, it runs the risks of legal battles against policies and regulations and makes its worldwide deployment much more difficult.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190314T153320Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190314T153320Z">
        <seg>Как заявляет Protocol Labs, файлы, размещенные в IPFS являются перманентными, не могут быть удалены, что может приводить к юридическим битвам в аспекте государственных политик и регуляторов, глобальное распространение файлов становится намного более сложным.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">At the same time, it punishes misbehaving participants.</prop>
      <prop type="next">This allows PPIO to make use of the vast amount of unused bandwidth and storage resources on the Internet, and provide robust storage service at much lower cost.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>As a result, a large, high-quality miner community can be established and kept growing.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190314T155341Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190314T155341Z">
        <seg>В результате может быть сформировано большое и качественное сообщество майнеров.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">Similarly, data distribution and retrieval are mostly handled by nearby peers as well.</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.5em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>As a result, data transfer can be maintained at much higher speed by fully utilizing local network bandwidth.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190320T105137Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190320T105137Z">
        <seg>В результате, транспортировка данных может осуществляться с намного более высокой скоростью за счет полной утилизации локальных каналов связи.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">When the user node is in a second location $B$, it finds neighbors in location $B$.</prop>
      <prop type="next">If the user node stays in location $A$ for an extended period, its neighbor list will contain more peers from location $A$, and vice versa.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>As a result, its neighbor list or history list contains peers from both locations.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190320T121235Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190320T121235Z">
        <seg>В результате, его список соседей и исторический список содержит пиров из обоих локаций.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">Therefore, the miners with lower bandwidth will not be incentivized to store popular content.</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.5em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>As a result, popular contents are mostly stored on the miners with higher bandwidth, which in turn improves the speed and experience when the user downloads such content.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190325T160849Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190325T160849Z">
        <seg>В результате, популярный контент в основном сосредоточится у майнеров с широким каналом, что приведет к увеличению скорости и удовлетворенности пользователя при скачивании такого контента.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">The list gets continuously updated by dropping disappeared nodes and adding newly joined neighbors.</prop>
      <prop type="next">With all the nodes following the same process as described below, the self-organizing P2P overlay network can be established and maintained.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>As a result, the list should mostly contain active and fast neighbors.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190320T111826Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190320T111826Z">
        <seg>В результате, список должен в основном содержать активных и быстрых соседей.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">•\quad Obtain new candidate neighbors from the Kademlia DHT.</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.8em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>As discussed in the previous section, there is no guarantee that these peers are its geographical neighbors or have a fast connection to the node.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190320T112617Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190320T112617Z">
        <seg>Как упоминалось ранее, нет гарантии что эти пиры расположены близко в географическом плане или обладают быстрым каналом связи к узлу.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">As storing popular content increases its chance to provide download service and get rewarded, the miner will proactively send requests to the scheduler to store the resources of popular content.</prop>
      <prop type="next">When a miner discovers that its stored content is no longer trendy, it can request to remove the content from its storage.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>As many miners follow the same strategy, popular data gets quickly populated, and it improves the download speed significantly for the users.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190325T145135Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190325T145135Z">
        <seg>Если множество майнеров будет следовать этой стратегии, популярные данные быстро распространятся, и это значительно увеличит скорость скачивания для пользователей.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\\ \\From the process above, a miner can track the requests of nearby users and identify popular content.</prop>
      <prop type="next">As many miners follow the same strategy, popular data gets quickly populated, and it improves the download speed significantly for the users.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>As storing popular content increases its chance to provide download service and get rewarded, the miner will proactively send requests to the scheduler to store the resources of popular content.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190325T145005Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190325T145005Z">
        <seg>Обладание популярным контентом увеличивает шанс того что он будет скачан и оплачен, майнер будет заранее слать запросы планировщику на сохранение ресурса популярного контента.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">Users in the same region have to compete for the available bandwidth from the data centers.</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.5em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>As the number of users grows, their transfer speed and user experience will likely degrade.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190320T103930Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190320T103930Z">
        <seg>При возростании количества пользователей будет деградировать скорость транспортировки и удовлетворенность этих самых пользователей.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">It not only provides more robust and efficient services than existing cloud-based storage platforms such as AWS S3 but also significantly reduces the storage cost.</prop>
      <prop type="next">PPIO's well-designed decentralized storage network and incentive mechanism allows it to make use of the vast amount of unused bandwidth and storage resources on the Internet, and provide reliable storage service at much lower cost.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>At the same time, PPIO also offers better data security and privacy protection.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190316T163727Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190314T120812Z">
        <seg>В то же время, PPIO предлагает лучшую защиту в аспектах безопасности и приватности.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">To make the storage system easy to use, PPIO introduces a scheme called "Coin Pool", that helps the users to store and download micropayments.</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.6em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>At the same time, PPIO's design also includes a mechanism to protect users from the impact of storage price fluctuations, which provides a better user experience than existing centralized storage platforms and more importantly much lower price.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190314T160636Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190314T160636Z">
        <seg>Так же, ахитектура PPIO включает механизм противостояния колебаниям цены хранения, предоставляющий пользователям лучший вариант чем существующие централизованные платформы хранения и, что не менее важно, по намного меньшей цене.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">These incidents pose a grave threat to not just the privacy of individual users, but also the security and integrity of the entire Internet.</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.5em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>At the same time, high bandwidth and storage cost is another inherent problem of the centralized storage systems, it leads to unaffordable price and makes it extremely difficult for many Internet companies to be profitable.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190314T141902Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190314T141130Z">
        <seg>Так же, другой проблемой централизованных систем хранения является высокая стоимость каналов связи и хранилищ, она приводит к неприемлемой цене и делает крайне сложным прибыльность для многих Интернет-компаний.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">By using data sharding and encryption algorithms, user's data can only be retrieved by the one who possesses the user's unique private key.</prop>
      <prop type="next">PPIO is equipped with practical storage proofs to maintain the integrity and reliability of its storage contents.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>At the same time, it allows the user to easily share their data to the public or within a private group.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190314T163352Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190314T163352Z">
        <seg>В то же время, они позволяют пользователю делиться данными публично или в приватной группе.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">However, too many concurrent downloads will exhaust the bandwidth resource of these miners and reduce the download speed of each user.</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.5em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>At the same time, it is not fair to the miners that store less popular content, that gets much lower reward than the others.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190325T155001Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190325T155001Z">
        <seg>В то же самое время, не вполне честно, что майнеры, хранящие менее популярный контент, получают много меньшее вознаграждение чем остальные.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">PPIO's well-designed incentives provide attractive financial rewards to miners and encourage them to contribute to the network.</prop>
      <prop type="next">As a result, a large, high-quality miner community can be established and kept growing.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>At the same time, it punishes misbehaving participants.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190314T155227Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190314T155227Z">
        <seg>В то же время, они наказывают неадекватных участников.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">In a data distribution network, a small number of popular content can consume a large portion of the bandwidth and storage resources.</prop>
      <prop type="next">Therefore, optimization of popular content distribution is crucial to the network.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>At the same time, the download speed of popular content can have a considerable impact on the overall user experience.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190325T140352Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190325T140352Z">
        <seg>В то же время, скорость скачивания популярного контента может иметь существенное значение на пользовательские впечатления в целом.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">Each downloading node sends download requests to multiple peers, manages downloaded pieces and deals with potential timeouts and failures from the peers.</prop>
      <prop type="next">By utilizing the two data-driven scheduling algorithms, PPIO's dynamic P2P network can handle an extremely high volume of concurrent data transmission efficiently.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>At the same time, the downloading node itself can be serving download requests, working as a peer to other nodes.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T143142Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T143142Z">
        <seg>В одно и тоже время скачивающий узел сам может обслуживать запросы на скачивание, работать как пир для других узлов.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">When a user node requests for a piece of data, it looks up the resources from the indexer node, and the indexer node returns information about the miner nodes that store the content.</prop>
      <prop type="next">Its peers will forward the request to their neighbors upon receiving it.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>At the same time, user node also broadcasts the request to its neighbors to find the resources.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190325T143007Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190325T143007Z">
        <seg>В то же самое время, для поиска желательного контента, пользовательский узел широковещательно опрашивает своих соседей.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\noindent</prop>
      <prop type="next">It significantly improves the overall transmission efficiency of the network, especially for TCP connections, as it works around the low-efficiency problem caused by TCP's conservative flow control.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>Based on the experience of building the high-performing P2P network, PPIO's design allows multiple connections to be established from each peer.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T101624Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T101624Z">
        <seg>С учетом опыта разработки высоко производительных одноранговых сетей, PPIO спроектирована таким образом чтобы с каждым пиром устанавливалось множество соединений.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">•\quad {\bf Scalability and High Efficiency.} Benefit from the founding team's experience from creating and operating the distributed network with hundreds of millions of users, PPIO is designed from the ground up to perform efficiently at a global scale.</prop>
      <prop type="next">PPIO's design also improves the efficiency in regional networks and makes it more friendly to ISPs.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>Besides a set of industry proven P2P transmission technologies, the team also developed data-driven scheduling, a self-organizing overlay network, and optimized content distribution network.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190316T163110Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190314T161722Z">
        <seg>Наряду с множеством проверенных в промышленных условиях одноранговых технологий передачи, команда так же разработала планировщик, управляемый данными (data-driven scheduling), самоорганизующуюся оверлейную сеть и сеть оптимального распространения контента.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">Each node needs to maintain two real-time lists to support the above process, a list of current neighbors, and a list of neighbor candidates.</prop>
      <prop type="next">These are essential to node selection in the overlay network.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>Besides, each node also maintains a list of past neighbors.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190320T113948Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190320T113948Z">
        <seg>Так же, каждый узел поддерживает список бывших соседей.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">For that purpose, its file index is made public to facilitate features like Web access, but it poses a challenge to preserving user privacy and data security in a storage network.</prop>
      <prop type="next">It does borrow mature P2P system designs from proven applications such as BitTorrent, but it provides no good solution to handle complex network environments and does not offer performance optimization within regional networks.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>Besides, some of its storage proofs are too complex and likely to hold the system back from running efficiently at a large scale.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190314T152009Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190314T152009Z">
        <seg>Кроме того, некоторые из криптомеханизмы слишком сложны и предположительно будут негативно сказываться при большом масштабе системы.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">Some of the known issues of Storj are the lack of quick response from miners upon storage request and its transactions are settled once per month which is not friendly to the miners.</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.5em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>BurstCoin utilizes Proof of Capacity (PoC) that does take storage capacity of the miners into account, but unfortunately, it is not enough to serve well for the storage requirements.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190314T150203Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190314T150203Z">
        <seg>BurstCoin использует Proof of Capacity (PoC), учитывающий размер хранилищ майнеров, но, к сожалению, этого не достаточно для нормального функционирования хранилища с выполнением всех требований к нему.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">To avoid unnecessary burden on the network, the length of the forwarding path is limited.</prop>
      <prop type="next">When not enough nodes have been reached, a longer forwarding path is allowed.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>But it also adapts based on the number of nodes that the request has reached.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190325T143441Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190325T143441Z">
        <seg>Но, так же, количество пересылок адаптируется по количеству узлов, которых запрос достиг.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">PPIO's founding team successfully developed PPLive, and they were also behind its innovative P2P network design and efficient data transmission technologies\cite{article4}\cite{article5}\cite{article6}\cite{article7}.</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.5em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>By leveraging the experience, PPIO's P2P network is designed to be a robust, scalable and high-performing data storage and transmission system.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T090012Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T090012Z">
        <seg>С учетом этого опыта, одноранговая сеть PPIO спроектирована робастной, масштабируемой быстродействующей системой хранения и передачи данных.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">•\quad {\bf Privacy, Security and Stability.} Data security and privacy protection are the top requirements in PPIO's distributed file system design.</prop>
      <prop type="next">At the same time, it allows the user to easily share their data to the public or within a private group.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>By using data sharding and encryption algorithms, user's data can only be retrieved by the one who possesses the user's unique private key.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190314T163252Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190314T163252Z">
        <seg>За счет алгоритмов шардинга и шифрования, пользовательские данные могут быть получены только обладателем приватного ключа пользователя.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">At the same time, the downloading node itself can be serving download requests, working as a peer to other nodes.</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.7em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>By utilizing the two data-driven scheduling algorithms, PPIO's dynamic P2P network can handle an extremely high volume of concurrent data transmission efficiently.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T143334Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T143334Z">
        <seg>Используя эти два алгоритма планирования, управляемые данными, динамическая одноранговая сеть PPIO может эффективно обрабатывать значительные объемыконкуррентно передаваемых данных.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">PPIO's design also improves the efficiency in regional networks and makes it more friendly to ISPs.</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.6em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>Combined with its innovation in NAT Traversal, Kademlia distributed hash table (DHT), lightweight storage consensus proof and optimized transmission for media streaming, PPIO's distributed storage network can perform with extremely high efficiency and can be easily scaled to hundreds of millions of network nodes.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190316T163439Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190316T163439Z">
        <seg>Комбинируя свои иннвации с такими технологиями как обход NAT (NAT Traversal), распределенные хэш-таблицы (DHT) Kademlia, облегченное доказательство консенсуса хранилища и оптимизированное потоковое
вещание медиа, распределенная сеть хранения PPIO может быть крайне эффективной и может быть легко масштабирована на сотни миллионов сетевых узлов.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\\ \\The algorithm to identify popular content can be customized by each miner.</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.5em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>Different miners in different regions can customize the algorithm differently, to optimize for higher reward.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190325T154027Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190325T154027Z">
        <seg>Различные майнеры в разных регионах могут модифицировать алгоритм по разному, для максимизации вознаграждения.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">The deployment of Amazon AWS data centers is shown in Figure 2.3.</prop>
      <prop type="next">Users in the same region have to compete for the available bandwidth from the data centers.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>Due to the ad hoc nature of the Internet, it is challenging to guarantee fast data transfer everywhere in the world by relying on a handful of data centers.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190320T103455Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190320T103455Z">
        <seg>В связи со специфичной природой интернета, довольно трудно гарантировать высокую скорость передачи данных в каждой точке земного шара, полагаясь на несколько дата-центров.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">It significantly improves the robustness of the distributed storage system and allows the client to download data from the closest neighbors on the network.</prop>
      <prop type="next">In section 2 of this chapter, PPIO's P2P network design will be explained in details, including its intelligent data-driven scheduling algorithms, its implementation of the Distributed Hash Table (DHT), its traffic management based on Proactive Network Provider Participation (P4P), and its P2P based content distribution technology(PCDN).</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>Due to the unique nature of the P2P network, more copies of the data lead to faster download speed.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190318T172155Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190316T173008Z">
        <seg>Из за уникальной особенности одноранговой сети, наличие множества копий данных приводит к более высокой скорости загрузки.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">Each peer responds to multiple download requests, and potentially to multiple downloading nodes.</prop>
      <prop type="next">At the same time, the downloading node itself can be serving download requests, working as a peer to other nodes.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>Each downloading node sends download requests to multiple peers, manages downloaded pieces and deals with potential timeouts and failures from the peers.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T143041Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T143041Z">
        <seg>Каждый скачивающий узел посылает запросы на скачивание множеству пиров, контролирует скаченные части и наблюдает за возможными истечениями времени ожидания и сбоями пиров.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\noindent</prop>
      <prop type="next">Besides, each node also maintains a list of past neighbors.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>Each node needs to maintain two real-time lists to support the above process, a list of current neighbors, and a list of neighbor candidates.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190320T113918Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190320T113918Z">
        <seg>Для выполнения изложенного выше процесса, каждый узел должен поддерживать в реальном времени два списка, список текущих соседей и список соседей-кандидатов.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">The algorithm steps through the network path and finds nodes closer to the key on every step to look up a specific key-value pair in the network until it reaches the node that stores the key-pair.</prop>
      <prop type="next">Such distance is calculated by taking an XOR operation on two Node IDs.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>Each node needs to store information of a group of other nodes based their distance to it to support the lookup.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190320T095141Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190320T094325Z">
        <seg>Для поддержки такого поиска, каждый узел должен содержать информацию о группе других узлов на основе их дистанции.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">No single participating node in the DHT is tasked to maintain the entire network.</prop>
      <prop type="next">Redundancy is also added to the data and stored on multiple nodes to maintain the reliability of the system so that a single node failure does not cause loss of data.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>Each node only stores a small part of the database and only needs to maintain information of its adjacent nodes, such design significantly reduces each node’s bandwidth and resource usage.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T161303Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T160345Z">
        <seg>Каждый узел сохраняет лишь малую часть базы данных, нуждается в обслуживании информации только о соседних узлах, такой дизайн существенно снижает необходимую ширину канала связи и использование ресурсов каждого узла.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">•\quad Attempt to make connections to the above two sets of candidate nodes, the number of connections cannot exceed a given limit.</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.8em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>Each of the connected nodes is now considered a neighbor.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190320T112926Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190320T112926Z">
        <seg>Каждый соединенный узел считается соседом.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">For example, one segment can be partitioned into M pieces, and these pieces can be duplicated and stored by N different storage miners.</prop>
      <prop type="next">A scheduler decides how the M pieces can be downloaded from the N peers so that the segment can be retrieved in a fast, efficient manner, and avoid duplicated pieces to be downloaded.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>Each of these N miners is also called a “Peer”.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T093456Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T093456Z">
        <seg>Каждый их этих N майнеров так же называется “Пиром (Peer)”.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">PPIO's P2P transmission network is fully dynamic.</prop>
      <prop type="next">Each downloading node sends download requests to multiple peers, manages downloaded pieces and deals with potential timeouts and failures from the peers.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>Each peer responds to multiple download requests, and potentially to multiple downloading nodes.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T142801Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T142801Z">
        <seg>Каждый пир отвечает на множество запросов на скачивание, и, потенциально, множеству скачивающих узлов.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">In PPIO‘s system, a storage "Object" is divided into "Segments", each "Segment" is further divided into some "Pieces".</prop>
      <prop type="next">Each of these N miners is also called a “Peer”.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>For example, one segment can be partitioned into M pieces, and these pieces can be duplicated and stored by N different storage miners.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T093420Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T093420Z">
        <seg>Например, один сегмент может быть разбит на M частей, и эти части могут быть продублированы и сохранены в N различных хранилищах майнеров.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">The data breach has become frequently occurred, with an ever-growing scale and impact.</prop>
      <prop type="next">These incidents pose a grave threat to not just the privacy of individual users, but also the security and integrity of the entire Internet.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>For example, the Dropbox hacking in 2016 alone leaked 68 million user accounts.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190314T130019Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190314T130019Z">
        <seg>Например, в 2016 году был взломан Dropbox, что привело к утечке 68 миллионов пользовательстких аккаунтов.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\\ \\The emerging FileCoin project that is under development by Protocol Labs adds an incentive layer on top of Inter-planetary File System (IPFS), with the goal to build a storage infrastructure and protocol to replace HTTP protocol.</prop>
      <prop type="next">Besides, some of its storage proofs are too complex and likely to hold the system back from running efficiently at a large scale.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>For that purpose, its file index is made public to facilitate features like Web access, but it poses a challenge to preserving user privacy and data security in a storage network.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190314T151822Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190314T151822Z">
        <seg>Для этой цели индекс файлов делается публичным, что создает возможности наподобие Веб-доступа к файлам, но это, так же, создает проблему сохранения приватности пользователя и безопасности данных в сети.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">In the traditional Client-Server (CS) model, the server can quickly become the network bottleneck when the client population grows.</prop>
      <prop type="next">In such a network, multiple copies of the data are distributed and stored on many different nodes.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>However, a decentralized peer-to-peer network does not rely on any central server to function correctly, and can easily tolerate the fault and failure of some nodes.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190316T172533Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190316T172533Z">
        <seg>Однако, децентрализованная одноранговая сеть не зависит от какого либо центрального сервера для того чтобы корректно функционировать и способна легко переносить ошибки и отказы некоторых узлов.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\\ \\With the DHT implementation above, structured data such as file index, statistics on network nodes, and other metadata can be securely saved and quickly looked up in PPIO’s distributed network.</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.5em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>However, data transfer in its storage network is handled differently, which will be discussed in the next section.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190320T102156Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190320T102113Z">
        <seg>Тем не менее, транспортировка данных в сети хранения происходит по другому, это бкдет освещено далее.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">The global cloud storage market has grown enormously in recent years and will continue to grow at a faster pace.</prop>
      <prop type="next">The data breach has become frequently occurred, with an ever-growing scale and impact.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>However, the existing centralized solutions have many problems.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190314T125521Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190314T125521Z">
        <seg>Тем не менее, существующие централизованные решения имеют множество проблем.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">PPIO incentives the nodes based on their contributions of storage and bandwidth, therefore the nodes incline to stay in the network and make a long and reliable contribution \cite{article1}.</prop>
      <prop type="next">Section 3 of this chapter explains PPIO's Proof of Replication (PoRep), Proof of Download (PoD), Proof of Spacetime (PoSt), and Light Proof of Capacity (LPoC) that are designed to defend the network against all these attacks and maintain the integrity of the system.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>However, the malicious nodes would attempt to cheat the network through various types of attacks, which undermines the system fairness.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T082631Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T082631Z">
        <seg>Тем не менее, злонамеренные узлы предпринимают попытки причинить вред сети посредством различных типов атак, подрывающих целостность системы.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\\ \\There have been many attempts to build distributed storage systems.</prop>
      <prop type="next">Siacoin is one of the attempts that is built on top of Bitcoin-like Proof of Work (PoW) consensus.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>However, these attempts were not successful.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190314T142512Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190314T142512Z">
        <seg>Тем не менее, эти попытки не были успешными.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\\ \\The miner nodes that store a large amount of popular content are likely to receive more download requests, and fulfilling those requests gets them higher rewards.</prop>
      <prop type="next">At the same time, it is not fair to the miners that store less popular content, that gets much lower reward than the others.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>However, too many concurrent downloads will exhaust the bandwidth resource of these miners and reduce the download speed of each user.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190325T154737Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190325T154737Z">
        <seg>Однако, чрезмерное конкуррентное скачивание будет переполять пропускную способность этих майнеров и приводить к уменьшению скорости скачивания для каждого пользователя.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">The user always prefers the ones that provide higher download speed.</prop>
      <prop type="next">The amount of data it uploads to the users will decrease, which in turn decreases the reward it receives.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>If a miner does not have enough bandwidth, users will switch to others.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190325T160531Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190325T160436Z">
        <seg>Если майнер не обладает достаточной шириной канала, пользователи переключаться на других.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">UDP based protocols such as KCP or UDT\cite{article13} are attempted first to make the connection.</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.8em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>If it fails, TCP based protocols will be used instead to adapt to different types of heterogeneous networks.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T095125Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T095125Z">
        <seg>Если она оказывается неудачной, для адаптации в различных типах гетерогенных сетей будет использоваться протокол на основе TCP.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">2.\quad For each peer, an expected download speed $V_{conn}$ is calculated based on its transmission history.</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.8em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>If no history is found, a default empirical value is used.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T095307Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T095307Z">
        <seg>В случае отсутствия исторических данных используется эмпирическое значение по умолчанию.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">If the user node stays in location $A$ for an extended period, its neighbor list will contain more peers from location $A$, and vice versa.</prop>
      <prop type="next">In this way, when user node uploads data, neighbor miners from both nodes will store copies of the data, so that fast data retrieval can be achieved in both places.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>If the user node repeatedly travels back and forth, the list will contain the similar number of peers from location $A$ and $B$.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190320T121444Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190320T121444Z">
        <seg>Если пользователь постоянно перемещается туда и обратно, список будет содержать примерно одинаковое число пиров как из $A$ так и из $B$.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">As a result, its neighbor list or history list contains peers from both locations.</prop>
      <prop type="next">If the user node repeatedly travels back and forth, the list will contain the similar number of peers from location $A$ and $B$.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>If the user node stays in location $A$ for an extended period, its neighbor list will contain more peers from location $A$, and vice versa.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190320T121340Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190320T121340Z">
        <seg>Если пользователь остается в локации $A$ на длительный период, его список соседей будет содержать больше пиров локации $A$, и наоборот.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\\ \\When a miner node receives the forwarded request, and if it happens to possess the requested resources, it notifies the user and there is better priority that user will ,in fact, download the data from it, since the miner node is in the forwarding path of the user’s neighbors, and thus close to the user.</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.5em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>In PPIO, the miner is incentivized to provide download service as it gets rewarded for doing so.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190325T144441Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190325T144441Z">
        <seg>В PPIO майнер мотивирован предоставлять услугу скачивания так как получает за нее вознаграждение.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">1\% \cite{article4}</prop>
      <prop type="next">For example, one segment can be partitioned into M pieces, and these pieces can be duplicated and stored by N different storage miners.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>In PPIO‘s system, a storage "Object" is divided into "Segments", each "Segment" is further divided into some "Pieces".</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T093237Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T091019Z">
        <seg>В системе PPIO, хранимый "Объект (Object)" разбивается на "Сегменты (Segments)", каждый "Сегмент" далее разбивается на несколько "Честей (Pieces)".</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\subsubsection{Optimized Distribution of Popular Content}  %——2.2.4</prop>
      <prop type="next">At the same time, the download speed of popular content can have a considerable impact on the overall user experience.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>In a data distribution network, a small number of popular content can consume a large portion of the bandwidth and storage resources.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190325T140245Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190325T140245Z">
        <seg>В сети распространения данных, малое количество популярного контента может занять большую часть пропускной способности сети и ресурсов хранилищ.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">The estimated arrival time for each piece can be calculated based on the speed of each virtual connection and the remaining pieces to be downloaded in each queue.</prop>
      <prop type="next">An illustration of the pre-allocation algorithm is shown in Figure 2.1.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>In general, pieces with higher priority should end up with an earlier estimated arrival time.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T113515Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T113225Z">
        <seg>Главное, более приоритетные части должны оканчиваться с более ранним временем доставки.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">Due to the unique nature of the P2P network, more copies of the data lead to faster download speed.</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.6em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>In section 2 of this chapter, PPIO's P2P network design will be explained in details, including its intelligent data-driven scheduling algorithms, its implementation of the Distributed Hash Table (DHT), its traffic management based on Proactive Network Provider Participation (P4P), and its P2P based content distribution technology(PCDN).</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190318T172140Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190318T172008Z">
        <seg>В секции 2 данной главы будет детально рассмотрена архитектура одноранговой сети PPIO, включая интеллектуальные алгоритмы планирования предачи данных, основанные на самих данных (ntelligent data-driven scheduling algorithms), реализация распределенной хэш-таблицы (DHT), управление трафиком на основе упредительного учета структуры сети (Proactive Network Provider Participation, P4P), а так же, технологии доставки контента для одноранговых сетей (P2P based content distribution technology, PCDN).</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">However, a decentralized peer-to-peer network does not rely on any central server to function correctly, and can easily tolerate the fault and failure of some nodes.</prop>
      <prop type="next">It significantly improves the robustness of the distributed storage system and allows the client to download data from the closest neighbors on the network.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>In such a network, multiple copies of the data are distributed and stored on many different nodes.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190316T172704Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190316T172704Z">
        <seg>Данные в такой сети распространяются и хранятся в виде множества копий на множестве узлов.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">•\quad {\bf  P2P Network:} PPIO constructs a self-governing, resilient and scalable P2P network that allows the participating nodes to easily share idle or unused bandwidth, storage, and computation resources.</prop>
      <prop type="next">However, a decentralized peer-to-peer network does not rely on any central server to function correctly, and can easily tolerate the fault and failure of some nodes.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>In the traditional Client-Server (CS) model, the server can quickly become the network bottleneck when the client population grows.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190316T172113Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190316T172113Z">
        <seg>В традиционной модели клиент-сервер (Client-Server, CS), сервер может быстро стать узким местом в сети при росте популяции клиентов.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">The download requests of the remaining pieces will be re-routed to other peers.</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.5em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>In this case, the non-responding peer will also be penalized, and the number of connections that can be established from the peer in future downloads is reduced.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T101049Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T101015Z">
        <seg>В этом случае не-отвечающий пир будет оштрафован, будет уменьшено количество соединений, устанавливаемых к пиру при будущих скачиваниях.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">The pieces at the anchor point are prioritized during download, to improve the user experience.</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.6em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>In this case, there is a higher chance that necessary pieces are already downloaded to allow the playback to start immediately after seeking.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T111610Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T111308Z">
        <seg>В этом случае значительно повышается вероятностьтого,  что необходимые части уже будут загружены, что позволит начать воспроизведение немедленно после пере-позиционирования.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\subsection{Technology Highlights} %——2.1</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.6em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>In this chapter, three core technologies behind PPIO will be elaborated:</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190316T164605Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190316T164605Z">
        <seg>В данной главе будут рассмотрены три основные технологии, используемые в PPIO:</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">New copies are created for existing user data in the network, and these copies are stored by prioritizing the new neighbors.</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.5em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>In this way, fast data retrieval can be achieved for previously stored data, as well as new data to be stored to the network.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190320T122453Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190320T122453Z">
        <seg>В этом случае, для ранее сохраненных данных может быть обеспечено быстрое получение так же, как и для вновь сохраняемых в сети данных .</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">If the user node repeatedly travels back and forth, the list will contain the similar number of peers from location $A$ and $B$.</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.5em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>In this way, when user node uploads data, neighbor miners from both nodes will store copies of the data, so that fast data retrieval can be achieved in both places.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190320T121631Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190320T121631Z">
        <seg>В этом случае, когда узел пользователя выгружает данные, соседние майнеры из обоих локаций будут сохранять их копии, таким образом, быстро получить данные можно будет в обоих местах.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\\ \\This method is driven by the demand, and it incentivizes miners to store popular content proactively.</prop>
      <prop type="next">As PPIO’s overlay network is built by clustering nearby peers, if a piece of content is only popular in a certain region, only the miners in the same region populate it extensively.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>It also adapts to the popularity of data in different regions.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190325T145631Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190325T145631Z">
        <seg>Так же, он адаптирован для популяризации данных в разных регионах.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">These key-value pairs are distributed and stored among the participating nodes.</prop>
      <prop type="next">No single participating node in the DHT is tasked to maintain the entire network.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>It avoids the problem with the centralized database system, where a failure in the central server leads to the breakdown of the entire network.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T160048Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T160048Z">
        <seg>Это предотвращает проблемы централизованных систем БД, при которых отказ центрального сервера приводит к отказу всей сети.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">PPIO's consensus algorithm is designed by its use scenario.</prop>
      <prop type="next">It improves the efficiency of the network, protects its integrity and enables it to operate in a secure, decentralized manner.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>It calculates the power of the miners based on their storage and bandwidth contributions, selects a block producer randomly via Verifiable Random Function (VRF)\cite{article24}\cite{article25}, utilizes Byzantine Fault Tolerance (BFT) based consortium consensus for validation.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T084858Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T084858Z">
        <seg>Она вычисляет мощность майнеров на основе их вклада в хранение и пропускную способность, затем случайным образом выбирает генератора следующего блока на основании Проверяемой Случайной Функции (Verifiable Random Function,VRF)\cite{article24}\cite{article25}, для проверки которой использоуется консенсус на основе консорциума Византийских Генералов (Byzantine Fault Tolerance, BFT).</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">Besides, some of its storage proofs are too complex and likely to hold the system back from running efficiently at a large scale.</prop>
      <prop type="next">Such deficiency in the design can lead to many real-world problems to the miners and ISPs.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>It does borrow mature P2P system designs from proven applications such as BitTorrent, but it provides no good solution to handle complex network environments and does not offer performance optimization within regional networks.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190314T152459Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190314T152459Z">
        <seg>FileCoin использует архитектуру одноранговых сетей из проверенных временем приложений, таких как BitTorrent, но, не предоставляет решений для сложных сетевых сред и не предлагает скоростных оптимизаций для региональных сетей.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">It provides in-depth details on its distributed file system, network architecture, and storage workflow.</prop>
      <prop type="next">\newpage</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>It explains how PPIO can prevent various network attacks, and discusses how it establishes a healthy and sustainable incentive mechanism, economic model and ecosystem.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190314T154604Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190314T124731Z">
        <seg>Документ разъясняет как PPIO противостоит различным сетевым атакам, поддерживает работоспособность и устойчивость механизма поощрений, предлагает экономическую модельи экосистему.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">It calculates the power of the miners based on their storage and bandwidth contributions, selects a block producer randomly via Verifiable Random Function (VRF)\cite{article24}\cite{article25}, utilizes Byzantine Fault Tolerance (BFT) based consortium consensus for validation.</prop>
      <prop type="next">It is also the foundation of PPIO's high-volume, large-scale storage market.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>It improves the efficiency of the network, protects its integrity and enables it to operate in a secure, decentralized manner.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T085032Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T085032Z">
        <seg>Это увеличивает эффективность сети, защищает ее целостность и позволяет действовать безопасно.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">It improves the efficiency of the network, protects its integrity and enables it to operate in a secure, decentralized manner.</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.5em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>It is also the foundation of PPIO's high-volume, large-scale storage market.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T085146Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T085146Z">
        <seg>Так же, это является основой многообъемного и сильно масштабируемого рынка хранилищ PPIO.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">PPIO is a programmable decentralized storage and delivery network.</prop>
      <prop type="next">At the same time, PPIO also offers better data security and privacy protection.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>It not only provides more robust and efficient services than existing cloud-based storage platforms such as AWS S3 but also significantly reduces the storage cost.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190314T120525Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190314T120525Z">
        <seg>Она не только предоставляет более мощные и эффективные службы, нежели существующие облачные платформы хранения данных, такие как AWS S3, но, так же, значительно снижает стоимость хранения. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\\ \\ In this work, PPIO's design goals are explained, followed by the details on how it achieves these goals.</prop>
      <prop type="next">It explains how PPIO can prevent various network attacks, and discusses how it establishes a healthy and sustainable incentive mechanism, economic model and ecosystem.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>It provides in-depth details on its distributed file system, network architecture, and storage workflow.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190314T124320Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190314T124320Z">
        <seg>Документ предоставляет низкоуровневую подробную информацию о распределенной файловой системе, архитектуре сети и процесса хранения.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">Based on the experience of building the high-performing P2P network, PPIO's design allows multiple connections to be established from each peer.</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.5em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>It significantly improves the overall transmission efficiency of the network, especially for TCP connections, as it works around the low-efficiency problem caused by TCP's conservative flow control.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T102140Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T102140Z">
        <seg>Это существенно увеличивает эффективность передачи сети в целом, особенно для TCP соединений, работая как заплатка над проблемой малой эффективности, привносимой консервативным управлением потоком передачи данных в TCP.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">In such a network, multiple copies of the data are distributed and stored on many different nodes.</prop>
      <prop type="next">Due to the unique nature of the P2P network, more copies of the data lead to faster download speed.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>It significantly improves the robustness of the distributed storage system and allows the client to download data from the closest neighbors on the network.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190316T172848Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190316T172848Z">
        <seg>Это значительно повышает устойчивость системы распределенного хранения и позволяет клиентам получать данные с ближайших соседних узлов в сети.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">At the same time, user node also broadcasts the request to its neighbors to find the resources.</prop>
      <prop type="next">To avoid unnecessary burden on the network, the length of the forwarding path is limited.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>Its peers will forward the request to their neighbors upon receiving it.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190325T143156Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190325T143156Z">
        <seg>По факту получения они будут пересылать запрос далее своим соседям.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">PPIO is equipped with practical storage proofs to maintain the integrity and reliability of its storage contents.</prop>
      <prop type="next">An optimized Proof of Space-Time (PoSt) ensures that the specified data is indeed stored by the miner over a period.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>Light Proof of Capacity (LPoC) is developed to provide lightweight validation of storage capacity provided by the miners.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190314T163742Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190314T163742Z">
        <seg>Облегченное доказательство вместимости (Light Proof of Capacity, LPoC) разработано для легкого удостоверения в наличии заданного объема свободного места в распоряжении майнера.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">•\quad The anchor point.</prop>
      <prop type="next">The pieces at the anchor point are prioritized during download, to improve the user experience.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>Many media streaming applications allow random access playbacks such as fast forwarding or seeking.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T110025Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T110025Z">
        <seg>Многие приложения медиа-вещания позволяют проигрывание с произвольного места, например для перемотки или поиска.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">As PPIO’s overlay network is built by clustering nearby peers, if a piece of content is only popular in a certain region, only the miners in the same region populate it extensively.</prop>
      <prop type="next">Thus the overall efficiency of the storage network is maintained.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>Miners in other parts of the network are not affected.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190325T150114Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190325T150114Z">
        <seg>Майнеры из других частей сети не затрагиваются.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\\ \\ PPIO’s distributed storage is a self-organizing, unstructured overlay network, that encourages connection among local peers.</prop>
      <prop type="next">Similarly, data distribution and retrieval are mostly handled by nearby peers as well.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>Nearby storage miners are more likely to be selected to store the data.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190320T104940Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190320T104940Z">
        <seg>Для хранения данных с большой вероятностью будут выбраны майнеры, расположенные рядом.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">When the reset is initiated, its neighbor list is rebuilt from scratch.</prop>
      <prop type="next">In this way, fast data retrieval can be achieved for previously stored data, as well as new data to be stored to the network.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>New copies are created for existing user data in the network, and these copies are stored by prioritizing the new neighbors.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190320T122228Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190320T122228Z">
        <seg>Для пользовательских данных в сети создаются новые копии, и эти копии сохраняются с приоритезацией новых соседей.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">•\quad Start by selecting an initial set of candidate neighbors among the peers with which it had connections in the past.</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.8em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>Newly joined nodes start with an empty list.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190320T112326Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190320T112326Z">
        <seg>Вновь присоединенные узлы начинают с пустым списком.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">It avoids the problem with the centralized database system, where a failure in the central server leads to the breakdown of the entire network.</prop>
      <prop type="next">Each node only stores a small part of the database and only needs to maintain information of its adjacent nodes, such design significantly reduces each node’s bandwidth and resource usage.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>No single participating node in the DHT is tasked to maintain the entire network.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T160150Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T160150Z">
        <seg>Обслуживанием всей сети озадачен не один узел-участник.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">Such distance is calculated by taking an XOR operation on two Node IDs.</prop>
      <prop type="next">Therefore, the distance between node IDs and keys can be calculated in the same way.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>Node IDs have the same bit length as the keys used in key-value pairs.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190320T094500Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190320T094500Z">
        <seg>Идентификаторы узлов имеют такую же длину как и ключи, используемые в парах ключ-значение.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">When a miner discovers that its stored content is no longer trendy, it can request to remove the content from its storage.</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.5em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>Once approved, the storage can be released and made available to store other resources.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190325T145358Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190325T145358Z">
        <seg>После этого хранилище становится доступным для сохранения других ресурсов.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">The miner nodes with higher bandwidth and larger storage still have enough incentives to do so, but they won’t download too much such content.</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.7em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>Otherwise, they can no longer achieve a surplus by providing download service that their bandwidth allows them to.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190325T161845Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190325T160050Z">
        <seg>Иначе, они не смогут обслуживать избыточные данные предоставлением услуги скачивания, умещающуюся в ширину канала.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\\</prop>
      <prop type="next">These changes are mainly caused by nodes via parallel looking over disjoint paths.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>PPIO also adopts an extension of Kademlia-S/Kademlia\cite{article23}to improve the security of the network.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190320T095958Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190320T095958Z">
        <seg>Так же, для увеличения безопасности сети, PPIO применяет расширение Kademlia-S/Kademlia\cite{article23}.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">•\quad {\bf Strong Application Support and Ecosystem.} PPIO provides a set of storage APIs similar to those of the cloud services such as AWS S3 and makes the data migration from those services much comfortable.</prop>
      <prop type="next">PPIO has a comprehensive plan to develop a robust, healthy and sustainable ecosystem, to facilitate the development of applications and services, and allow the developers to enjoy real benefits from PPIO's growth.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>PPIO also has a set of technologies built into better support decentralized applications, including object-based storage, dApp Sandbox mechanisms, and file access management, etc.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190314T165338Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190314T165338Z">
        <seg>PPIO так же имеет некоторые технологии для улучшения поддержки распределенных приложений, включая хранилища объектов, механизм песочницы, управление доступом к файлам и т.п.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">PPIO is a fully decentralized storage and distribution system that requires its database to be also managed in a decentralized fashion.</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.5em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>PPIO employs Distributed Hash Table (DHT) to store data and provide routing and lookup services.\\</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T155233Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T155233Z">
        <seg>Для хранения данных, роутинга и поиска сервисов PPIO применяет Распределенную хэш-таблицу (Distributed Hash Table, DHT).\\</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">PPIO also has a set of technologies built into better support decentralized applications, including object-based storage, dApp Sandbox mechanisms, and file access management, etc.</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-1em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>PPIO has a comprehensive plan to develop a robust, healthy and sustainable ecosystem, to facilitate the development of applications and services, and allow the developers to enjoy real benefits from PPIO's growth.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190314T165827Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190314T165827Z">
        <seg>PPIO имеет обстоятельный план для разработки сильной, живучей и устойчивой экосистемы для разработки приложений и сервисов, и предоставления разработчикам возможности наслаждаться бенефитами роста PPIO.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">•\quad {\bf Proof:} The nodes of the traditional P2P network are free to choose join or leave the network, it is difficult to maintain the stability of the network.</prop>
      <prop type="next">However, the malicious nodes would attempt to cheat the network through various types of attacks, which undermines the system fairness.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>PPIO incentives the nodes based on their contributions of storage and bandwidth, therefore the nodes incline to stay in the network and make a long and reliable contribution \cite{article1}.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T082625Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T082625Z">
        <seg>PPIO поощряет узлы в зависимости от реализуемых ими ресурсов хранилища и пропускной способности, тем самым узлы стремятся оставаться в сети и производить длительный и стабильный вклад \cite{article1}.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\subsubsection{Distributed Database and Routing}  %——2.2.2 \cite{article17}</prop>
      <prop type="next">PPIO employs Distributed Hash Table (DHT) to store data and provide routing and lookup services.\\</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>PPIO is a fully decentralized storage and distribution system that requires its database to be also managed in a decentralized fashion.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T155103Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T154518Z">
        <seg>PPIO является полностью распределенной системой хранения и распространения данных, нуждающаяся в том чтобы ее база данных так же управлялась в децентрализованном виде.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\noindent\\</prop>
      <prop type="next">It not only provides more robust and efficient services than existing cloud-based storage platforms such as AWS S3 but also significantly reduces the storage cost.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>PPIO is a programmable decentralized storage and delivery network.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190314T142418Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190314T120051Z">
        <seg>PPIO является программируемой децентрализованной сетью хранения и доставки данных.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">PPIO's unique decentralized file system prevents unauthorized access and ensures that all the data can be stored securely and privately.</prop>
      <prop type="next">PPIO meets the storage needs of both today's Internet businesses and services, and the emerging decentralized applications (DApps).</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>PPIO is designed from the ground up to perform efficiently on a global scale, by leveraging the founding team's experience from designing and running the decentralized network with hundreds of millions of users.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190314T123229Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190314T123229Z">
        <seg>PPIO спроектирована с нуля для эффективного функционирования в глобальном масштабе, на основании опыта команды разработчиков в проектировании и запуске децентрализованной сети с сотнями миллионов пользователей.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">At the same time, it allows the user to easily share their data to the public or within a private group.</prop>
      <prop type="next">Light Proof of Capacity (LPoC) is developed to provide lightweight validation of storage capacity provided by the miners.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>PPIO is equipped with practical storage proofs to maintain the integrity and reliability of its storage contents.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190314T163517Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190314T163517Z">
        <seg>Для обеспечения целостности и доступности хранимого контента, PPIO снабжена практичными механизмами доказывания.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">PPIO is designed from the ground up to perform efficiently on a global scale, by leveraging the founding team's experience from designing and running the decentralized network with hundreds of millions of users.</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.5em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>PPIO meets the storage needs of both today's Internet businesses and services, and the emerging decentralized applications (DApps).</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190314T123515Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190314T123515Z">
        <seg>PPIO сводит потребности в хранении данных, имеющиеся у сегодняшнего бизнеса с одной стороны и предлагаемых возможностей поставщиков соответствующих услуг с другой, а так же, предоставляет возможность реализации распределенных приложений (DApps).</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">Therefore, optimization of popular content distribution is crucial to the network.</prop>
      <prop type="next">The two methods are designed to work together and ensure the efficient distribution of popular content and maintain a healthy ecosystem of the storage network.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>PPIO provides two optimized scheduling methods for popular content, one is storage miners active selection, and the other is enforced by the scheduler(indexer node).</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190325T142138Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190325T140723Z">
        <seg>PPIO предоставляетдва оптимизированных метода планирования доставки популярного контента, один из них, это "активнй выбор майнера" (Storage miners active selection), второй форсируется планировщиком (индексным узлом) ???.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\\ \\ There are many different implementations of DHT, some of the commonly used are Chord\cite{article14}, Pastry\cite{article15}, Tapestry\cite{article18}, Dynamo\cite{article19}, and Kademlia\cite{article16}.</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.5em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>PPIO uses Kademlia, so do many other well-known P2P projects like PPLive, BitTorrent, eMule, etc.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T161829Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T161829Z">
        <seg>PPIO использует вариант Kademlia, так же, как многие другие хорошо известные P2P проекты - PPLive, BitTorrent, eMule и т.п..</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\noindent</prop>
      <prop type="next">Each peer responds to multiple download requests, and potentially to multiple downloading nodes.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>PPIO's P2P transmission network is fully dynamic.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T142703Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T142703Z">
        <seg>Одноранговая сеть передачи PPIO полностью динамична.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">•\quad {\bf Consensus: } Popular blockchain consensus algorithms such as Proof of Work (PoW), Proof of Stake (PoS) and Delegated Proof of Stake (DPoS) all make trade-offs in decentralization, security and performance.</prop>
      <prop type="next">It calculates the power of the miners based on their storage and bandwidth contributions, selects a block producer randomly via Verifiable Random Function (VRF)\cite{article24}\cite{article25}, utilizes Byzantine Fault Tolerance (BFT) based consortium consensus for validation.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>PPIO's consensus algorithm is designed by its use scenario.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T084156Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T084156Z">
        <seg>Алгоритм консенсуса PPIO спроектирован в соответствии со сценарием использования самого PPIO.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\\ \\Besides to supporting efficient file download, PPIO also supports optimized P2P data streaming.</prop>
      <prop type="next">The technology has gone through many iterations of trial-and-error optimizations and is proven to provide high-quality user experience to streaming applications such as video-on-demand (VOD) service.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>PPIO's data-driven scheduler is designed to provide stable real-time streaming performance in an ad-hoc P2P network\cite{article12}.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T102949Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T102949Z">
        <seg>Планировщик PPIO, управляемый данными, спроектирован для стабильной работы потокового вещания реального времени в специализированной одноранговой сети\cite{article12}.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">Besides a set of industry proven P2P transmission technologies, the team also developed data-driven scheduling, a self-organizing overlay network, and optimized content distribution network.</prop>
      <prop type="next">Combined with its innovation in NAT Traversal, Kademlia distributed hash table (DHT), lightweight storage consensus proof and optimized transmission for media streaming, PPIO's distributed storage network can perform with extremely high efficiency and can be easily scaled to hundreds of millions of network nodes.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>PPIO's design also improves the efficiency in regional networks and makes it more friendly to ISPs.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190316T163237Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190316T163237Z">
        <seg>Архитектура PPIO, так же, направлена на увеличение эффектирвности  работы в региональных сетях, что делает ее более дружелюбной к поставщикам интернета (ISP).</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">So it is what PPIO attempts to accomplish.</prop>
      <prop type="next">Such experiences allow the team to develop efficient and practical solutions to achieve the following design goals.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>PPIO's founding team successfully designed, developed and maintained PPLive, a peer to peer streaming system that serves hundreds of millions of users on a daily basis.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190314T154036Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190314T154036Z">
        <seg>Команда, учредившая и разрабатывающая PPIO успешно спроектировала, разработала и поддерживает PPLive, одноранговую систему вещания, обслуживающую сотни миллионов пользователей ежедневно.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\subsection{P2P Network} %——2.2 \cite{article4}\cite{article5}\cite{article6}\cite{article7}</prop>
      <prop type="next">By leveraging the experience, PPIO's P2P network is designed to be a robust, scalable and high-performing data storage and transmission system.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>PPIO's founding team successfully developed PPLive, and they were also behind its innovative P2P network design and efficient data transmission technologies\cite{article4}\cite{article5}\cite{article6}\cite{article7}.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T085847Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T085604Z">
        <seg>Команда PPIO ранее успешно разработала проект PPLive, и он так же был основан на инновационном дизайне одноранговой сети и эффективных технологиях передачи данных\cite{article4}\cite{article5}\cite{article6}\cite{article7}.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">PPIO's well-designed decentralized storage network and incentive mechanism allows it to make use of the vast amount of unused bandwidth and storage resources on the Internet, and provide reliable storage service at much lower cost.</prop>
      <prop type="next">PPIO is designed from the ground up to perform efficiently on a global scale, by leveraging the founding team's experience from designing and running the decentralized network with hundreds of millions of users.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>PPIO's unique decentralized file system prevents unauthorized access and ensures that all the data can be stored securely and privately.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190314T122818Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190314T122818Z">
        <seg>Уникальная децентрализованная файловая система PPIO предоствращает неавторизованный доступ и гарантирует безопасность и приватность хранения данных.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">At the same time, PPIO also offers better data security and privacy protection.</prop>
      <prop type="next">PPIO's unique decentralized file system prevents unauthorized access and ensures that all the data can be stored securely and privately.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>PPIO's well-designed decentralized storage network and incentive mechanism allows it to make use of the vast amount of unused bandwidth and storage resources on the Internet, and provide reliable storage service at much lower cost.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190314T154535Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190314T121201Z">
        <seg>Грамотно продуманная распределенная сеть хранения и механизм поощрения позволяют PPIO использовать значительный объем неиспользованной полосы пропускания и ресурсы хранилищ в сети Интернет, а так же, предоставлять надежные услуги хранения с намного меньшей ценой.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">•\quad  {\bf Low Storage Cost.} In the future, high storage cost is one of the critical challenges for many companies.</prop>
      <prop type="next">At the same time, it punishes misbehaving participants.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>PPIO's well-designed incentives provide attractive financial rewards to miners and encourage them to contribute to the network.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190314T155051Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190314T155051Z">
        <seg>Грамотно спроектированные поощрения в PPIO предоставляют привлекательные винансовые вознаграждения майнерам и провоцируют их на взаимодействие с сетью.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">Siacoin is one of the attempts that is built on top of Bitcoin-like Proof of Work (PoW) consensus.</prop>
      <prop type="next">Storj is another project that has gone through years of development, but it remains in the testing phase.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>PoW introduces wasteful computation and energy consumption, and it does not take into account the different levels of storage and bandwidth contribution among the miners, which are crucial to a decentralized distributed storage system.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190314T143019Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190314T143019Z">
        <seg>PoW предполагает производство массивных вычислений, тем самым форсирует потребление большого количества энергии, а так же, он не учитывает объемы хранилищ и мощность каналов связи майнеров, являющихся ключевыми аспектами в децентрализованной распределенной системе хранения данных.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">Proof of Replication (PoRep) is used to guarantee that the miners replicate user's data.</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.6em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>Proof of Download (PoD) ensures that user can download the stored data correctly.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190314T164242Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190314T164150Z">
        <seg>Доказательство получения (Proof of Download, PoD) убеждает пользователя в том что он может корректно получить хранимые майнером данные.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">An optimized Proof of Space-Time (PoSt) ensures that the specified data is indeed stored by the miner over a period.</prop>
      <prop type="next">Proof of Download (PoD) ensures that user can download the stored data correctly.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>Proof of Replication (PoRep) is used to guarantee that the miners replicate user's data.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190314T164043Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190314T164043Z">
        <seg>Доказательство пересылки (Proof of Replication, PoRep) гарантирует то что майнет реплицировал пользовательские данные.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">Each node only stores a small part of the database and only needs to maintain information of its adjacent nodes, such design significantly reduces each node’s bandwidth and resource usage.</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.5em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>Redundancy is also added to the data and stored on multiple nodes to maintain the reliability of the system so that a single node failure does not cause loss of data.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T161535Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T161535Z">
        <seg>Так же, в данные добавляется избыточность, для обеспечения надежности системы данные сохраняются на нескольких узлах, таким образом отказ отдельного узла не приводит к потере данных.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">However, the malicious nodes would attempt to cheat the network through various types of attacks, which undermines the system fairness.</prop>
      <prop type="next">The optimized and secure implementation of the proofs allows them to function efficiently at large scale, that enables the incentive system to operate in securely and help establish a healthy decentralized distributed storage market and economic system.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>Section 3 of this chapter explains PPIO's Proof of Replication (PoRep), Proof of Download (PoD), Proof of Spacetime (PoSt), and Light Proof of Capacity (LPoC) that are designed to defend the network against all these attacks and maintain the integrity of the system.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T083220Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T083220Z">
        <seg>Секция 3 данной главы раскрывает такие механизмы доказывания в PPIO как Доказательство пересылки (Proof of Replication, PoRep), Доказательство получения данных (Proof of Download, PoD), Доказательство хранения данных в течении времени (Proof of Spacetime, PoSt) и Облегченное доказательство вместимости (Light Proof of Capacity, LPoC), спроектированные для защиты сети против всех этих атак и поддержания целостности системы.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\\ \\With more nodes joining PPIO’s storage network, it becomes easier for each node to find nearby peers with a faster connection, for both storage and retrieval.</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.5em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>Server bandwidth is no longer a bottleneck, and user growth leads to better speed and experience.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190320T105454Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190320T105454Z">
        <seg>Ширина канала связи сервера более не является узким местом и пользователи получают лучшю скорость и удовлетворенность.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">However, these attempts were not successful.</prop>
      <prop type="next">PoW introduces wasteful computation and energy consumption, and it does not take into account the different levels of storage and bandwidth contribution among the miners, which are crucial to a decentralized distributed storage system.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>Siacoin is one of the attempts that is built on top of Bitcoin-like Proof of Work (PoW) consensus.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190314T150337Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190314T142633Z">
        <seg>Одна из таких попыток, Seacoin, построенная на основе Бикоин-подобного консенсуса Proof of Work (PoW).</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">Nearby storage miners are more likely to be selected to store the data.</prop>
      <prop type="next">As a result, data transfer can be maintained at much higher speed by fully utilizing local network bandwidth.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>Similarly, data distribution and retrieval are mostly handled by nearby peers as well.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190320T105032Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190320T105032Z">
        <seg>Аналогично, распространение и получение данных в основном обрабатывается рядом стоящими пирами.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">Therefore, the distance between node IDs and keys can be calculated in the same way.</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.3em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>Since the XOR distance does not take actual geographic distance into account, it is possible for two nodes to reside next to one another in the network even though one of them may be in the United Kingdom, while the other is in the United States.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190320T095729Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190320T095729Z">
        <seg>Так как XOR-дистанция не учитывает реальную географическую дистанцию, узлы в сети могут считаться близкими даже если один из них расположен в Великобритании а другой в США.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\\ \\From the discussions above, it is clear that a more complete decentralized distributed storage solution is yet to be built to support large-scale and real-world storage system.</prop>
      <prop type="next">PPIO's founding team successfully designed, developed and maintained PPLive, a peer to peer streaming system that serves hundreds of millions of users on a daily basis.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>So it is what PPIO attempts to accomplish.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190314T153747Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190314T153747Z">
        <seg>Вот чего пытается достигнуть PPIO.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">Storj is another project that has gone through years of development, but it remains in the testing phase.</prop>
      <prop type="next">BurstCoin utilizes Proof of Capacity (PoC) that does take storage capacity of the miners into account, but unfortunately, it is not enough to serve well for the storage requirements.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>Some of the known issues of Storj are the lack of quick response from miners upon storage request and its transactions are settled once per month which is not friendly to the miners.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190314T145927Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190314T143205Z">
        <seg>Некоторые из известных проблем Storj - это невозможность получения быстрого ответа от майнеров относительно запросов на хранение, а так же их транзакций, фиксируемых раз в месяц, что не является удобным для майнеров.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">PoW introduces wasteful computation and energy consumption, and it does not take into account the different levels of storage and bandwidth contribution among the miners, which are crucial to a decentralized distributed storage system.</prop>
      <prop type="next">Some of the known issues of Storj are the lack of quick response from miners upon storage request and its transactions are settled once per month which is not friendly to the miners.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>Storj is another project that has gone through years of development, but it remains in the testing phase.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190314T143154Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190314T143154Z">
        <seg>Storj, другой проект, разрабатываемый вот уже в течении нескольких лет, но так и не вышедший из фазы тестирования.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">•\quad Sequential download.</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.8em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>Subsequent segments and pieces from the current point of playback need to be prioritized in download scheduling, to maintain smooth streaming playback.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T104542Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T104336Z">
        <seg>Для гладкого проигрывания потока, планировщик скачивания должен приоритезировать последующие сегменты и части от текущей точки воспроизведения.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">It does borrow mature P2P system designs from proven applications such as BitTorrent, but it provides no good solution to handle complex network environments and does not offer performance optimization within regional networks.</prop>
      <prop type="next">As Protocol Labs claims that files stored on IPFS are permanent and cannot be deleted, it runs the risks of legal battles against policies and regulations and makes its worldwide deployment much more difficult.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>Such deficiency in the design can lead to many real-world problems to the miners and ISPs.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190314T152706Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190314T152706Z">
        <seg>Такие ущербности в заимствованной архитектуре могут приводить ко множеству проблем в реальном использовании, как для майнеров так и для поставщиков интернета (Internet Service Providers, ISPs).</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">Each node needs to store information of a group of other nodes based their distance to it to support the lookup.</prop>
      <prop type="next">Node IDs have the same bit length as the keys used in key-value pairs.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>Such distance is calculated by taking an XOR operation on two Node IDs.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190320T094417Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190320T094417Z">
        <seg>Такая дистанция вычисляется применением операции XOR над двумя идентификаторами узлов.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">PPIO's founding team successfully designed, developed and maintained PPLive, a peer to peer streaming system that serves hundreds of millions of users on a daily basis.</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.6em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>Such experiences allow the team to develop efficient and practical solutions to achieve the following design goals.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190314T154155Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190314T154155Z">
        <seg>Такой опыт позволяет команде разрабатывать эффективное и практичное решение, направленное на следующие цели.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">The node ID is also used to calculate the distance between nodes and locate key-value pairs.</prop>
      <prop type="next">Each node needs to store information of a group of other nodes based their distance to it to support the lookup.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>The algorithm steps through the network path and finds nodes closer to the key on every step to look up a specific key-value pair in the network until it reaches the node that stores the key-pair.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190320T094207Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T162246Z">
        <seg>Алгоритм итерационно строит путь в сети, на каждой итерации отыскивая узлы, ближайшие к ключу исмкомой пары ключ-значение в сети до тех пор пока не достигнет узла, хранящего искомую пару ключ-значение.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">If a miner does not have enough bandwidth, users will switch to others.</prop>
      <prop type="next">Therefore, the miners with lower bandwidth will not be incentivized to store popular content.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>The amount of data it uploads to the users will decrease, which in turn decreases the reward it receives.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190325T160626Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190325T160626Z">
        <seg>Количество отгруженных пользователям данных уменьшится, что приведет к уменьшению полученного вознаграждения.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">However, the existing centralized solutions have many problems.</prop>
      <prop type="next">For example, the Dropbox hacking in 2016 alone leaked 68 million user accounts.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>The data breach has become frequently occurred, with an ever-growing scale and impact.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190314T125905Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190314T125905Z">
        <seg>Порча и утеря данных происходят все чаще, с постоянно растущим масштабом и влиянием.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">Under cost constraints, each of the services can only deploy a limited number of data centers around the world.</prop>
      <prop type="next">Due to the ad hoc nature of the Internet, it is challenging to guarantee fast data transfer everywhere in the world by relying on a handful of data centers.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>The deployment of Amazon AWS data centers is shown in Figure 2.3.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190320T102950Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190320T102950Z">
        <seg>На рисунке 2.3 показано распределение дата-центров Amazon AWS.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">6.\quad When a download request times out, the request is canceled, and all connections to the non-responding peer will be closed.</prop>
      <prop type="next">In this case, the non-responding peer will also be penalized, and the number of connections that can be established from the peer in future downloads is reduced.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>The download requests of the remaining pieces will be re-routed to other peers.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T100813Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T100813Z">
        <seg>Запросы на скачивание оставшихся частей будут переадресованы другим пирам.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">2.\quad Pieces to be downloaded are sorted based on their priorities and pre-allocated to available virtual connections by placing them in the corresponding download queues.</prop>
      <prop type="next">In general, pieces with higher priority should end up with an earlier estimated arrival time.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>The estimated arrival time for each piece can be calculated based on the speed of each virtual connection and the remaining pieces to be downloaded in each queue.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T113450Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T113024Z">
        <seg>Оценочное время доставки каждой части может быть вычеслено на основе информации о скорости каждого виртуального соединения и уже имеющихся частей к загрузке в каждой очереди.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\vspace{-0.5em}</prop>
      <prop type="next">However, the existing centralized solutions have many problems.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>The global cloud storage market has grown enormously in recent years and will continue to grow at a faster pace.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190314T125452Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190314T124912Z">
        <seg>Глобальный рынок облачных хранилищ в значительной мере вырос за последние годы и продолжает расти быстрыми темпами .</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\\ \\Every node in PPIO’s network maintains a list of neighboring peers to stay connected with.</prop>
      <prop type="next">As a result, the list should mostly contain active and fast neighbors.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>The list gets continuously updated by dropping disappeared nodes and adding newly joined neighbors.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190320T111739Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190320T111739Z">
        <seg>Список подвергается постоянному обновлению выбрасыванием отсоединившихся узлов и добавлением вновь присоединившихся соседей.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">The miners that request to store the most popular content need to pay the scheduler(indexer) before receiving the resources.</prop>
      <prop type="next">Otherwise, they can no longer achieve a surplus by providing download service that their bandwidth allows them to.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>The miner nodes with higher bandwidth and larger storage still have enough incentives to do so, but they won’t download too much such content.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190325T161617Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190325T155817Z">
        <seg>Узлы майнеров с широким каналом связи и большим объемом хранилища, имеют достаточно мотивации для такой оплаты, но не желают получать слишком много такого контента.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\\ \\To avoid these problems, the scheduler(indexer) in the network employs an adjusted scheduling service based on the popularity of the content.</prop>
      <prop type="next">The miner nodes with higher bandwidth and larger storage still have enough incentives to do so, but they won’t download too much such content.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>The miners that request to store the most popular content need to pay the scheduler(indexer) before receiving the resources.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190325T155627Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190325T155627Z">
        <seg>Майнеры, запрашивающие на хранение наиболее популярный контент, должны заплатить планировщику (индексеру) перед тем как получат ресурсы.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">These changes are mainly caused by nodes via parallel looking over disjoint paths.</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.5em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>The network can sustain attacks even when a large number of nodes are compromised.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190320T101747Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190320T101747Z">
        <seg>Сеть может противостоять атакам даже при большом количестве скомпромитированных узлов.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\\ \\Kademlia algorithm assigns a unique ID to each participating node.</prop>
      <prop type="next">The algorithm steps through the network path and finds nodes closer to the key on every step to look up a specific key-value pair in the network until it reaches the node that stores the key-pair.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>The node ID is also used to calculate the distance between nodes and locate key-value pairs.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T162113Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T162113Z">
        <seg>ID узла так же используется для вычисления дистанции между узлами и при размещении/поиске пар ключ-значение.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">Section 3 of this chapter explains PPIO's Proof of Replication (PoRep), Proof of Download (PoD), Proof of Spacetime (PoSt), and Light Proof of Capacity (LPoC) that are designed to defend the network against all these attacks and maintain the integrity of the system.</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.6em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>The optimized and secure implementation of the proofs allows them to function efficiently at large scale, that enables the incentive system to operate in securely and help establish a healthy decentralized distributed storage market and economic system.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T083748Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T083748Z">
        <seg>Оптимизированная и безопасная реализация доказательств позволяет им эффективно функционировать на больших масштабах, что дает возможность безопасно функционировать системе поощрений, помогая устанавливать здоровую среду для рынка и экономической системы распределенных хранилищ.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">Many media streaming applications allow random access playbacks such as fast forwarding or seeking.</prop>
      <prop type="next">In this case, there is a higher chance that necessary pieces are already downloaded to allow the playback to start immediately after seeking.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>The pieces at the anchor point are prioritized during download, to improve the user experience.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T111407Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T111244Z">
        <seg>Для улучшения восприятия пользователем, во время скачивания приоритезируются части в опорных точках.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">To achieve the design requirements above, a scheduling algorithm is required to make smart decisions on which peer a piece should be downloaded from, how many peers should be used for simultaneous download, how to set up the timer for each peer, how to reschedule remaining pieces and adapt to network changes, etc.</prop>
      <prop type="next">A summary of the scheduling algorithm is as follows:</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>The scheduler is also designed to maximize download speed and minimize the overhead of duplicated requests and data transmission.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T112141Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T112141Z">
        <seg>Так же, планировщик спроектирован для максимизации скорости загрузки и минимизации накладных расходов вследствие дублирования запросов и передачи данных.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">PPIO's data-driven scheduler is designed to provide stable real-time streaming performance in an ad-hoc P2P network\cite{article12}.</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.5em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>The technology has gone through many iterations of trial-and-error optimizations and is proven to provide high-quality user experience to streaming applications such as video-on-demand (VOD) service.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T103443Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T103443Z">
        <seg>Технология прошла сквозь множество итераций проб и ошибок и доказала способность предоставления пользователю высоко-качественной поддержки потоковых приложений, таких как службы видео-по-запросу (video-on-demand, VOD).</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">PPIO provides two optimized scheduling methods for popular content, one is storage miners active selection, and the other is enforced by the scheduler(indexer node).</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.5em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>The two methods are designed to work together and ensure the efficient distribution of popular content and maintain a healthy ecosystem of the storage network.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190325T142330Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190325T142330Z">
        <seg>Оба метода спроектированы для совместного функционирования и увеличения эффективности распространения популярного контента и поддержания здоровой экосистемы сети хранения.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">•\quad Unpopular pieces.</prop>
      <prop type="next">This may seem counterintuitive, but prioritizing these pieces will help make downloading of the entire segment much faster and get a better experience.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>The unpopular pieces (especially in media streaming) need to be prioritized during download.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T105311Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T105311Z">
        <seg>Непопулярные части (особенно при вещании медиа) нуждаются в приоритезации во время скачивания.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\\ \\ As shown in Fig 2.4, multiple miners store copies of the same data, they need to compete to provide download services to the user.</prop>
      <prop type="next">If a miner does not have enough bandwidth, users will switch to others.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>The user always prefers the ones that provide higher download speed.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190325T160328Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190325T160328Z">
        <seg>Пользователи всегда выбирают тех, кто предоставляет более высокую скорость скачивания.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">At the same time, the download speed of popular content can have a considerable impact on the overall user experience.</prop>
      <prop type="next">PPIO provides two optimized scheduling methods for popular content, one is storage miners active selection, and the other is enforced by the scheduler(indexer node).</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>Therefore, optimization of popular content distribution is crucial to the network.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190325T140502Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190325T140502Z">
        <seg>Таким образом, оптимизация доставки популярного контента является ключевым моментом в сети.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">Node IDs have the same bit length as the keys used in key-value pairs.</prop>
      <prop type="next">Since the XOR distance does not take actual geographic distance into account, it is possible for two nodes to reside next to one another in the network even though one of them may be in the United Kingdom, while the other is in the United States.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>Therefore, the distance between node IDs and keys can be calculated in the same way.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190320T095310Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190320T095310Z">
        <seg>Следовательно, дистанция между ID узла и ключем может быть вычислена таким же образом.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">The amount of data it uploads to the users will decrease, which in turn decreases the reward it receives.</prop>
      <prop type="next">As a result, popular contents are mostly stored on the miners with higher bandwidth, which in turn improves the speed and experience when the user downloads such content.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>Therefore, the miners with lower bandwidth will not be incentivized to store popular content.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190325T160710Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190325T160710Z">
        <seg>С другой стороны, майнеры с малой шириной канала не будут замотивированы на хранение популярного контента.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">Besides, each node also maintains a list of past neighbors.</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.5em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>These are essential to node selection in the overlay network.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190320T114200Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190320T114200Z">
        <seg>Все это является существенным для процедуры поиска узла в оверлейной сети.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">PPIO also adopts an extension of Kademlia-S/Kademlia\cite{article23}to improve the security of the network.</prop>
      <prop type="next">The network can sustain attacks even when a large number of nodes are compromised.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>These changes are mainly caused by nodes via parallel looking over disjoint paths.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190320T100754Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190320T100754Z">
        <seg>В основном, данные изменения вызваны узлами, использующими параллельный поиск над непересекающимися путями.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">For example, the Dropbox hacking in 2016 alone leaked 68 million user accounts.</prop>
      <prop type="next">At the same time, high bandwidth and storage cost is another inherent problem of the centralized storage systems, it leads to unaffordable price and makes it extremely difficult for many Internet companies to be profitable.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>These incidents pose a grave threat to not just the privacy of individual users, but also the security and integrity of the entire Internet.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190314T141102Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190314T141102Z">
        <seg>Такие инциденты представляют серьезную угрозу не только приватности отдельных пользователей, но, так же, безопасности и целостности всего Интернета.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\\In a DHT, each piece of data is bundled with a unique key into a key-value pair.</prop>
      <prop type="next">It avoids the problem with the centralized database system, where a failure in the central server leads to the breakdown of the entire network.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>These key-value pairs are distributed and stored among the participating nodes.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T160212Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T155531Z">
        <seg>Такие пары ключ-значение распространяются и хранятся на узлах-участниках сети.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">As a result, a large, high-quality miner community can be established and kept growing.</prop>
      <prop type="next">To make the storage system easy to use, PPIO introduces a scheme called "Coin Pool", that helps the users to store and download micropayments.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>This allows PPIO to make use of the vast amount of unused bandwidth and storage resources on the Internet, and provide robust storage service at much lower cost.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190314T155616Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190314T155616Z">
        <seg>Это позволяет PPIO задействовать большое количество неиспользуемой полосы пропускания каналов связи и ресурсов хранилищ в сети Интернет, предоставить мощную услугу хранения данных по сильно менщей цене.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">The unpopular pieces (especially in media streaming) need to be prioritized during download.</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.8em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>This may seem counterintuitive, but prioritizing these pieces will help make downloading of the entire segment much faster and get a better experience.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T105547Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T105547Z">
        <seg>Это может выглядеть контринтуитивно, но, приоритезация таких частей помогает более быстрому скачиванию всего сегмента оставляет у пользователя лучшие впечатления.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">A scheduler decides how the M pieces can be downloaded from the N peers so that the segment can be retrieved in a fast, efficient manner, and avoid duplicated pieces to be downloaded.</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.5em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>This process is called {\bf Multi-point Download Scheduling}.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T093816Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T093816Z">
        <seg>Данный процесс называется {\bf Планированием скачивания из многих источников (Multi-point Download Scheduling)}.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">Miners in other parts of the network are not affected.</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.5em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>Thus the overall efficiency of the storage network is maintained.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190325T150150Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190325T150150Z">
        <seg>Это обеспечивает эффективность сети хранения в целом.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\noindent</prop>
      <prop type="next">The scheduler is also designed to maximize download speed and minimize the overhead of duplicated requests and data transmission.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>To achieve the design requirements above, a scheduling algorithm is required to make smart decisions on which peer a piece should be downloaded from, how many peers should be used for simultaneous download, how to set up the timer for each peer, how to reschedule remaining pieces and adapt to network changes, etc.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T111931Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T111931Z">
        <seg>Для удовлетворения представленных выше требований дизайна, алгоритм планирования должен принимать взвешенные решения, от какого пира должна быть получена часть, как много пиров использовать для одновременной загрузки, как управлять таймером для каждого пира, как перепланировать оставшиеся части и адаптироваться к изменениям сети и т.п.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">Its peers will forward the request to their neighbors upon receiving it.</prop>
      <prop type="next">But it also adapts based on the number of nodes that the request has reached.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>To avoid unnecessary burden on the network, the length of the forwarding path is limited.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190325T143329Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190325T143329Z">
        <seg>Для предоствращения излишней нагрузки на сеть, количество пересылок ограничено.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">This allows PPIO to make use of the vast amount of unused bandwidth and storage resources on the Internet, and provide robust storage service at much lower cost.</prop>
      <prop type="next">At the same time, PPIO's design also includes a mechanism to protect users from the impact of storage price fluctuations, which provides a better user experience than existing centralized storage platforms and more importantly much lower price.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>To make the storage system easy to use, PPIO introduces a scheme called "Coin Pool", that helps the users to store and download micropayments.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190314T155748Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190314T155748Z">
        <seg>Для облегчения использования системы хранения, PPIO предлагает схему, называемую "Coin Pool", помогающую пользователям выгружать и загружать микроплатежи.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\vspace{-0.5em}</prop>
      <prop type="next">Under cost constraints, each of the services can only deploy a limited number of data centers around the world.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>Today’s well-established storage services, such as Amazon S3, Dropbox, Google Drive, iCloud, etc., store customer data in large-scale data centers.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190320T102806Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190320T102806Z">
        <seg>Современные промышленные сервисы хранения, такие как Amazon S3, Dropbox, Google Drive, iCloud и т.п., хранят пользовательские данные в больших дата-центрах.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">1.\quad Multiple virtual connections (Tunnels) are established between the user and each peer with the resources, to improve transmission efficiency.</prop>
      <prop type="next">If it fails, TCP based protocols will be used instead to adapt to different types of heterogeneous networks.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>UDP based protocols such as KCP or UDT\cite{article13} are attempted first to make the connection.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T094840Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T094840Z">
        <seg>Сначала предпринимается попытка соединения по протоколам, основанным на UDP, таким как KCP или UDT\cite{article13}.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">Today’s well-established storage services, such as Amazon S3, Dropbox, Google Drive, iCloud, etc., store customer data in large-scale data centers.</prop>
      <prop type="next">The deployment of Amazon AWS data centers is shown in Figure 2.3.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>Under cost constraints, each of the services can only deploy a limited number of data centers around the world.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190320T102920Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190320T102920Z">
        <seg>Из за дорогивизны, каждый такой сервис может разместить лишь ограниченное количество дата-центров по миру.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">Due to the ad hoc nature of the Internet, it is challenging to guarantee fast data transfer everywhere in the world by relying on a handful of data centers.</prop>
      <prop type="next">As the number of users grows, their transfer speed and user experience will likely degrade.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>Users in the same region have to compete for the available bandwidth from the data centers.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190320T103604Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190320T103604Z">
        <seg>Пользователяв одного региона приходится конкурировать за ширину канала связи к дата-центру.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">As many miners follow the same strategy, popular data gets quickly populated, and it improves the download speed significantly for the users.</prop>
      <prop type="next">Once approved, the storage can be released and made available to store other resources.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>When a miner discovers that its stored content is no longer trendy, it can request to remove the content from its storage.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190325T145246Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190325T145246Z">
        <seg>Когда майнер обнаружит что хранимый им контент больше не в тренде, он может запросить его удаление из своего хранилища.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\\ \\As described in section 2.2.3, a self-organizing overlay network is established by the participating nodes.</prop>
      <prop type="next">At the same time, user node also broadcasts the request to its neighbors to find the resources.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>When a user node requests for a piece of data, it looks up the resources from the indexer node, and the indexer node returns information about the miner nodes that store the content.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190325T142847Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190325T142847Z">
        <seg>Когда пользовательский узел запрашивает какую то часть данных, он в первую очередь отсматривает имеющиеся ресурсы на индексном узле, индексный узел возвращает информацию о узлах майнерах, хранящих желательный контент.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">A large percentage of the copies of the data are stored on the neighboring miners with a faster connection to the user, to achieve higher transfer speed during storage and retrieval.</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.5em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>When enough miner nodes join the network in different regions of the world, high data transfer speed can be maintained around the globe.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190320T115244Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190320T115218Z">
        <seg>Когда достаточное количество узлов майнеров подключится к сети в различных регионах мира, высокая скорость скорость передачи данных может быть достигнута в рамках всей планеты.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">But it also adapts based on the number of nodes that the request has reached.</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.5em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>When not enough nodes have been reached, a longer forwarding path is allowed.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190325T143613Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190325T143613Z">
        <seg>Дальнейшие пересылки разрешены до тех пор, пока не достигнуто достаточное количество узлов.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\\ \\When a user node permanently relocates to a different region, PPIO provides a reset feature to help with the reschedule.</prop>
      <prop type="next">New copies are created for existing user data in the network, and these copies are stored by prioritizing the new neighbors.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>When the reset is initiated, its neighbor list is rebuilt from scratch.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190320T122005Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190320T122005Z">
        <seg>При активации сброса, список соседей перестраивается с нуля.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">When the user node is in location $A$, it finds neighbors in location $A$.</prop>
      <prop type="next">As a result, its neighbor list or history list contains peers from both locations.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>When the user node is in a second location $B$, it finds neighbors in location $B$.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190320T121130Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190320T121130Z">
        <seg>Аналогично, при находжении пользователя в локации $B$,он находит соседей в локации $B$.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\\ \\When a user node repeatedly travels between two different regions, PPIO’s design can provide a great user experience in both places.</prop>
      <prop type="next">When the user node is in a second location $B$, it finds neighbors in location $B$.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>When the user node is in location $A$, it finds neighbors in location $A$.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190320T121134Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190320T121039Z">
        <seg>При нахождении пользователя в локации $A$, он находит соседей в этой самой локации $A$.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">As a result, the list should mostly contain active and fast neighbors.</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.8em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>With all the nodes following the same process as described below, the self-organizing P2P overlay network can be established and maintained.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190320T112042Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190320T112042Z">
        <seg>В случае если все узлы следуют описанному выше сценарию, формируется и поддерживается само-организующаяся одноранговая оверлейная сеть.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\vspace{-1.5em}</prop>
      <prop type="next">The user always prefers the ones that provide higher download speed.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>\\ \\ As shown in Fig 2.4, multiple miners store copies of the same data, they need to compete to provide download services to the user.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190325T160250Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190325T160250Z">
        <seg>\\ \\ Как показано на рис 2.4, множество майнеров хранят копии одних и тех же данных, они должны конкурировать за предоставление пользователям услуги скачивания.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\vspace{-0.5em}</prop>
      <prop type="next">It provides in-depth details on its distributed file system, network architecture, and storage workflow.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>\\ \\ In this work, PPIO's design goals are explained, followed by the details on how it achieves these goals.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190314T124127Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190314T124019Z">
        <seg>\\ \\ В данном документе разъясняются основные цели архитектуры PPIO, а так же, приводятся подробности методов достижения этих целей.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\\ \centerline{{Figure 2.3 AWS global infastructure}}</prop>
      <prop type="next">Nearby storage miners are more likely to be selected to store the data.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>\\ \\ PPIO’s distributed storage is a self-organizing, unstructured overlay network, that encourages connection among local peers.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190320T104403Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190320T104403Z">
        <seg>\\ \\ Распределенное хранилище PPIO является само организующейся, бесструктурной оверлейной сетью, со стимуляцией взаимодействия между локальными пирами.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\vspace{-0.5em}</prop>
      <prop type="next">PPIO uses Kademlia, so do many other well-known P2P projects like PPLive, BitTorrent, eMule, etc.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>\\ \\ There are many different implementations of DHT, some of the commonly used are Chord\cite{article14}, Pastry\cite{article15}, Tapestry\cite{article18}, Dynamo\cite{article19}, and Kademlia\cite{article16}.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T161705Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T161643Z">
        <seg>\\ \\ Существует множество различных реализаций DHT, вот некоторые наиболее используемые: Chord\cite{article14}, Pastry\cite{article15}, Tapestry\cite{article18}, Dynamo\cite{article19} и Kademlia\cite{article16}.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\vspace{-0.5em}</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.3em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>\\ \\ {\bf Environment variables of the pre-allocation algorithm}</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T142617Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T142605Z">
        <seg>\\ \\ {\bf Данные для алгоритма предварительного распределения}</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\vspace{-0.5em}</prop>
      <prop type="next">\begin{algorithm}[H]</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>\\ \\ {\bf Pseudocode}\\</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T143354Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T143354Z">
        <seg>\\ \\ {\bf Псевдокод}\\</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\vspace{-0.5em}</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.5em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>\\ \\ {\bf Real-time Data Streaming}</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T102337Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T102337Z">
        <seg>\\ \\ {\bf Вещание данных в реальном времени (Real-time Data Streaming)}</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\vspace{-0.5em}</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.8em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>\\ \\A P2P streaming system has the following unique design characteristics:</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T104429Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T103518Z">
        <seg>\\ \\Одноранговая система потокового вещания обладает следующими уникальными характеристиками дизайна:</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\vspace{-0.5em}</prop>
      <prop type="next">When a user node requests for a piece of data, it looks up the resources from the indexer node, and the indexer node returns information about the miner nodes that store the content.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>\\ \\As described in section 2.2.3, a self-organizing overlay network is established by the participating nodes.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190325T142549Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190325T142549Z">
        <seg>\\ \\Как описывалось в секции 2.2.3, между узлами-участниками формируется само-организующаяся оверлейная сеть.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\vspace{-0.5em}</prop>
      <prop type="next">PPIO's data-driven scheduler is designed to provide stable real-time streaming performance in an ad-hoc P2P network\cite{article12}.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>\\ \\Besides to supporting efficient file download, PPIO also supports optimized P2P data streaming.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T102512Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T102512Z">
        <seg>\\ \\Наряду с поддержкой эффективного скачивания файлов, PPIO так же поддерживает оптимизированное одноранговое потоковое вещание данных.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\vspace{-0.5em}</prop>
      <prop type="next">The list gets continuously updated by dropping disappeared nodes and adding newly joined neighbors.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>\\ \\Every node in PPIO’s network maintains a list of neighboring peers to stay connected with.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190320T111508Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190320T111508Z">
        <seg>\\ \\Каждый узел в сети PPIO обслуживает список соседних пиров с которыми он соединен.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\vspace{-0.5em}</prop>
      <prop type="next">So it is what PPIO attempts to accomplish.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>\\ \\From the discussions above, it is clear that a more complete decentralized distributed storage solution is yet to be built to support large-scale and real-world storage system.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190314T153647Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190314T153647Z">
        <seg>\\ \\Из изложенного выше становится понятно, что готовая децентрализованная распределенная система хранения, способная поддерживать высокое масштабирование и задачи реального мира, еще не построена.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\vspace{-0.5em}</prop>
      <prop type="next">As storing popular content increases its chance to provide download service and get rewarded, the miner will proactively send requests to the scheduler to store the resources of popular content.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>\\ \\From the process above, a miner can track the requests of nearby users and identify popular content.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190325T144605Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190325T144605Z">
        <seg>\\ \\В описанном выше процессе майнер может отслеживать запросы расположенных рядом пользователей и идентифицировать популярный контент.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\vspace{-0.5em}</prop>
      <prop type="next">The node ID is also used to calculate the distance between nodes and locate key-value pairs.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>\\ \\Kademlia algorithm assigns a unique ID to each participating node.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T161925Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T161925Z">
        <seg>\\ \\Алгоритм Kademlia назначает каждому узлу-участнику уникальный идентификатор (ID).</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\vspace{-0.5em}</prop>
      <prop type="next">Different miners in different regions can customize the algorithm differently, to optimize for higher reward.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>\\ \\The algorithm to identify popular content can be customized by each miner.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190325T153915Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190325T150204Z">
        <seg>\\ \\Алгоритм идентификации популярного контента может быть изменен для каждого майнера.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\vspace{-0.5em}</prop>
      <prop type="next">For that purpose, its file index is made public to facilitate features like Web access, but it poses a challenge to preserving user privacy and data security in a storage network.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>\\ \\The emerging FileCoin project that is under development by Protocol Labs adds an incentive layer on top of Inter-planetary File System (IPFS), with the goal to build a storage infrastructure and protocol to replace HTTP protocol.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190314T154640Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190314T150406Z">
        <seg>\\ \\Новый проект FileCoin, разрабатываемый Protocol Labs, добавляет слой поощрений над Inter-planetary File System (IPFS), с целью построения инфраструктуры хранилищ и протокола для замены HTTP.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\vspace{-0.5em}</prop>
      <prop type="next">However, too many concurrent downloads will exhaust the bandwidth resource of these miners and reduce the download speed of each user.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>\\ \\The miner nodes that store a large amount of popular content are likely to receive more download requests, and fulfilling those requests gets them higher rewards.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190325T154456Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190325T154456Z">
        <seg>\\ \\Для узлов майнеров, хранящих большое количество популярного контента, желательно получать больше запросов на скачивание и удовлетворять эти запросычтобы получать большее вознаграждение.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\vspace{-0.5em}</prop>
      <prop type="next">However, these attempts were not successful.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>\\ \\There have been many attempts to build distributed storage systems.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190314T142358Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190314T142237Z">
        <seg>\\ \\Предпринималось не мало попыток построения распределенных систем хранения данных.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\vspace{-0.5em}</prop>
      <prop type="next">It also adapts to the popularity of data in different regions.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>\\ \\This method is driven by the demand, and it incentivizes miners to store popular content proactively.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190325T145532Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190325T145532Z">
        <seg>\\ \\Данный метод работает при наличии соответствующей необходимости и поощряет майнеров на проактивное обслуживание популярного контента.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\vspace{-0.5em}</prop>
      <prop type="next">The miners that request to store the most popular content need to pay the scheduler(indexer) before receiving the resources.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>\\ \\To avoid these problems, the scheduler(indexer) in the network employs an adjusted scheduling service based on the popularity of the content.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190325T161552Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190325T155318Z">
        <seg>\\ \\Для предотвращения этих проблем сетевой планировщик (индексер) предоставляет выделенную услугу планирования, основанную на популярности контента.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\vspace{-0.5em}</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.8em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>\\ \\Two data-driven scheduling algorithms are developed for Multi-point Download Scheduling:</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T093908Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T093908Z">
        <seg>\\ \\В рамках Multi-point Download Scheduling разработано два алгоритма планирования:</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\vspace{-0.5em}</prop>
      <prop type="next">In PPIO, the miner is incentivized to provide download service as it gets rewarded for doing so.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>\\ \\When a miner node receives the forwarded request, and if it happens to possess the requested resources, it notifies the user and there is better priority that user will ,in fact, download the data from it, since the miner node is in the forwarding path of the user’s neighbors, and thus close to the user.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190325T144325Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190325T144325Z">
        <seg>\\ \\Когда узел майнера получает такой пересылаемый запрос, и если он обладает запрошенным ресурсом, он оповещает пользователя и, по факту, существует большая вероятность, что пользователь будет загружать данные именно с этого майнера, так как узел майнера расположен на пути пересылки среди соседей пользователя, и, соответственно, близок к нему.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\vspace{-0.5em}</prop>
      <prop type="next">When the reset is initiated, its neighbor list is rebuilt from scratch.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>\\ \\When a user node permanently relocates to a different region, PPIO provides a reset feature to help with the reschedule.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190320T122727Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190320T121929Z">
        <seg>\\ \\В случае если узел пользователя перемещается в другой регион на постоянной основе, для облегчения перепланировки PPIO предлагает возможность сброса.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\vspace{-0.5em}</prop>
      <prop type="next">When the user node is in location $A$, it finds neighbors in location $A$.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>\\ \\When a user node repeatedly travels between two different regions, PPIO’s design can provide a great user experience in both places.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190320T120957Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190320T120132Z">
        <seg>\\ \\В случае если узел пользователя постоянно путешествует между двумя различными регионами, архитектура PPIO может предложить замечательное решение для удобства пользователя в обоих местах.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\vspace{-0.5em}</prop>
      <prop type="next">A large percentage of the copies of the data are stored on the neighboring miners with a faster connection to the user, to achieve higher transfer speed during storage and retrieval.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>\\ \\When user uploads data to PPIO's storage network, its neighbors with a closer network distance are prioritized when selecting storage miners to store the data.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190320T114813Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190320T114813Z">
        <seg>\\ \\Когда пользователь выгружает данные в сеть хранения PPIO, приоритет в выборе майнеров-хранителей для размещения данных отдается соседям с меньшей сетевой дистанцией.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\vspace{-0.5em}</prop>
      <prop type="next">Server bandwidth is no longer a bottleneck, and user growth leads to better speed and experience.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>\\ \\With more nodes joining PPIO’s storage network, it becomes easier for each node to find nearby peers with a faster connection, for both storage and retrieval.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190320T105347Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190320T105347Z">
        <seg>\\ \\Чем больше узлов присоединяется к сети хранения PPIO, тем легче узлам становится отыскивать ближайших пиров с быстрыми соединениями, как для сохранения так и для получения данных.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\vspace{-0.5em}</prop>
      <prop type="next">However, data transfer in its storage network is handled differently, which will be discussed in the next section.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>\\ \\With the DHT implementation above, structured data such as file index, statistics on network nodes, and other metadata can be securely saved and quickly looked up in PPIO’s distributed network.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190320T102004Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190320T102004Z">
        <seg>\\ \\С приведенной выше реализацией DHT, такие структурированные данные как индекс файлов, статистики сетевых узлов и другие метаданные могут быть безопасно сохранены и быстро обнаруживаемы в  распределенной сети PPIO.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\vspace{-0.5em}</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.5em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>\\ \\{\bf About users who change regions frequently}</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190320T115320Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190320T115320Z">
        <seg>\\ \\{\bf Пользователи, часто меняющие регион пребывания}</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\vspace{-0.5em}</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.5em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>\\ \\{\bf Enforced by the indexer}</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190325T154225Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190325T154225Z">
        <seg>\\ \\{\bf Форсирование индексером}</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\vspace{-0.5em}</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.5em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>\\ \\{\bf Establishing a Self-Organizing P2P Network}</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190320T111049Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190320T111049Z">
        <seg>\\ \\{\bf Формирование само-организующейся одноранговой сети (Establishing a Self-Organizing P2P Network)}</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\vspace{-0.5em}</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.8em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>\\ \\{\bf Facts about PPLive:}</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T090021Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T090021Z">
        <seg>\\ \\{\bf Факты о PPLive:}</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\vspace{-0.5em}</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.5em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>\\ \\{\bf If the user permanently relocates to a different region}</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190320T121734Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190320T121734Z">
        <seg>\\ \\{\bf Если пользователь окончательно перемещается в другой регион}</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\vspace{-0.5em}</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.5em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>\\ \\{\bf Preferred storage miners with a closer network distance}</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190320T114506Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190320T114506Z">
        <seg>\\ \\{\bf Приоритезация майнеров-хранителей с малой сетевой дистанцией (Preferred storage miners with a closer network distance)}</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\vspace{-0.5em}</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.5em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>\\ \\{\bf Storage miners active selection}</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190325T142423Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190325T142423Z">
        <seg>\\ \\{\bf Активный выбор майнера (Storage Miner active selection)}</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\\ \\ \centerline{\includegraphics[width=340pt]{fig3}}</prop>
      <prop type="next">\\ \\ PPIO’s distributed storage is a self-organizing, unstructured overlay network, that encourages connection among local peers.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>\\ \centerline{{Figure 2.3 AWS global infastructure}}</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190320T103956Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190320T103956Z">
        <seg>\\ \centerline{{Рисунок 2.3 Глобальная инфраструктура AWS}}</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\vspace{-0.5em}</prop>
      <prop type="next">These key-value pairs are distributed and stored among the participating nodes.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>\\In a DHT, each piece of data is bundled with a unique key into a key-value pair.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T155401Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T155401Z">
        <seg>\\В DHT каждый кусок данных снабжается уникальным ключем с образованием пары ключ-значения.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\\ \centerline{\includegraphics[width=320pt]{fig2}}</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.5em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>\\\\ \centerline{{Figure 2.2 Lookup in Kademlia DHT}}</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190320T095811Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190320T095811Z">
        <seg>\\\\ \centerline{{Рисунок 2.2 Поиск в DHT Kademlia}}</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\vspace{-0.6em}</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.6em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>\\\\Summary of the PPIO scheduling algorithm:</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T094246Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T094206Z">
        <seg>\\\\Алгоритм планирования PPIO в кратце:</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\centerline{\includegraphics[width=300pt]{fig4}}</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-1.5em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>\\\\\centerline{{Figure 2.4 Dispatch of Popular Content}}</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190325T160113Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190325T160113Z">
        <seg>\\\\\centerline{{Рисунок 2.4 Доставка популярного контента}}</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\noindent</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.6em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>\\{\bf File Download:}</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T094136Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T094136Z">
        <seg>\\{\bf Получение файлов (File Download):}</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\renewcommand{\baselinestretch}{1.2}</prop>
      <prop type="next">\noindent\\</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>\author {\centerline{\Large Abstract}}</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190314T115446Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190314T115446Z">
        <seg>\author {\centerline{\Large Аннотация}}</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\Return{$connRequestQueues$}</prop>
      <prop type="next">\end{algorithm}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>\caption{Pre-schedule for the upcoming Piece, the result of the scheduling exists in the download queue of each tunnel.}</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T143727Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T143624Z">
        <seg>\caption{Предварительное планирование очередной Части, результат планирования представлен в виде очереди-к-загрузке для каждого туннеля.}</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\label{circuit}</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-2.5em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>\centerline{{Figure 2.1 Illustration of pre-allocation}}</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T132902Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T132902Z">
        <seg>\centerline{{Рисунок 2.1 Иллюстрация предварительного распределения}}</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\newpage</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.5em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>\section{Introduction} %—1</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190314T124909Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190314T124739Z">
        <seg>\section{Введение} %—1</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\vspace{-1em}</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.5em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>\section{Solution} %——2</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190318T171615Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190318T171615Z">
        <seg>\section{Решение} %——2</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\vspace{-0.5em}</prop>
      <prop type="next">PPIO's founding team successfully developed PPLive, and they were also behind its innovative P2P network design and efficient data transmission technologies\cite{article4}\cite{article5}\cite{article6}\cite{article7}.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>\subsection{P2P Network} %——2.2 \cite{article4}\cite{article5}\cite{article6}\cite{article7}</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T085213Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T085213Z">
        <seg>\subsection{Одноранговая сеть (P2P Network)} %——2.2 \cite{article4}\cite{article5}\cite{article6}\cite{article7}</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\vspace{-0.5em}</prop>
      <prop type="next">In this chapter, three core technologies behind PPIO will be elaborated:</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>\subsection{Technology Highlights} %——2.1</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190316T164442Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190316T164442Z">
        <seg>\subsection{Основные технологии} %——2.1</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\vspace{-0.5em}</prop>
      <prop type="next">1\% \cite{article4}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>\subsubsection{Data Driven Scheduling}  %——2.2.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T090831Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T090831Z">
        <seg>\subsubsection{Планирование на основе данных (Data Driven Scheduling)}  %——2.2.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\end{algorithm}</prop>
      <prop type="next">PPIO is a fully decentralized storage and distribution system that requires its database to be also managed in a decentralized fashion.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>\subsubsection{Distributed Database and Routing}  %——2.2.2 \cite{article17}</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T162407Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T162407Z">
        <seg>\subsubsection{Распределенная база данных и маршрутизация (Distributed Database and Routing)}  %——2.2.2 \cite{article17}</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\vspace{-0.5em}</prop>
      <prop type="next">In a data distribution network, a small number of popular content can consume a large portion of the bandwidth and storage resources.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>\subsubsection{Optimized Distribution of Popular Content}  %——2.2.4</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190325T140057Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190325T140057Z">
        <seg>\subsubsection{Оптимизация доставки популярного контента}  %——2.2.4</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\vspace{-0.5em}</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.5em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>\subsubsection{P2P Self-organizing Overlay networks}  %——2.2.3</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190320T102246Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190320T102246Z">
        <seg>\subsubsection{Одноранговые самоорганизующиеся оверлейные сети (P2P Self-organizing Overlay networks)}  %——2.2.3</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\setlength{\parskip}{0em}%设置段落间距</prop>
      <prop type="next">\begin{document}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>\title{ \LARGE\bf PPIO: A Programmable P2P Storage and\\Delivery Network}  %———标题</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190314T115908Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190314T112832Z">
        <seg>\title{ \LARGE\bf PPIO: Программируемая одноранговая сеть\\хранения и доставки}  %———标题</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\usepackage{algpseudocode}</prop>
      <prop type="next">%\usepackage{xcolor}%——————————————————————改变文字颜色</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>\usepackage{hyperref}%——————————————————————目录超链接</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190325T134638Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T072221Z">
        <seg>\usepackage[unicode,naturalnames]{hyperref}%——————————————————————目录超链接</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\usepackage{algorithmicx}</prop>
      <prop type="next">\linespread{1.0} %—— 行间距</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>\usepackage{pxfonts}</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T073729Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T072126Z">
        <seg>%\usepackage{pxfonts}
\usepackage{libertine}
\usepackage{libertinust1math}
\usepackage[T2A,T1]{fontenc}
\usepackage[utf8]{inputenc}
\usepackage[english,russian]{babel}</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\noindent</prop>
      <prop type="next">PPIO's well-designed incentives provide attractive financial rewards to miners and encourage them to contribute to the network.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>•\quad  {\bf Low Storage Cost.} In the future, high storage cost is one of the critical challenges for many companies.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190314T154352Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190314T154352Z">
        <seg>•\quad  {\bf Малая цена хранения.} В будущем, высокая цена хранения данных будет одним из критичных вызовов для многих компаний.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\noindent</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.8em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>•\quad 1/10 the operation cost of the traditional data network;</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T090652Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T090341Z">
        <seg>•\quad Операционные расходы составляют 1/10 по сравнению с традиционными сетями;</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\noindent</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.5em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>•\quad 400PB storage combined P2P storage capacity;</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T090646Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T090532Z">
        <seg>•\quad Суммарная вместимость хранилищ одноранговых узлов составляет 400PB;</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\noindent</prop>
      <prop type="next">Each of the connected nodes is now considered a neighbor.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>•\quad Attempt to make connections to the above two sets of candidate nodes, the number of connections cannot exceed a given limit.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190320T112824Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190320T112824Z">
        <seg>•\quad Предпринимается попытка установить соединение с кандидатами из упомянутых выше двух множеств, при этом число соединений не должно превзойти установленный лимит.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\noindent</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.8em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>•\quad Eliminate neighbors that have the low-speed connection to the node or are no longer reachable.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190320T113500Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190320T113500Z">
        <seg>•\quad Более не доступные соседи, а так же соседи с малой скоростью соединения, исключаются.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\noindent</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.8em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>•\quad File Download</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T094000Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T094000Z">
        <seg>•\quad Получение файлов (File Download)</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\noindent</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-1.5em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>•\quad Media streaming on demand\cite{article4}</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T094024Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T094024Z">
        <seg>•\quad Потоковое вещание по заказу (Media streaming on demand)\cite{article4}</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\noindent</prop>
      <prop type="next">As discussed in the previous section, there is no guarantee that these peers are its geographical neighbors or have a fast connection to the node.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>•\quad Obtain new candidate neighbors from the Kademlia DHT.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190320T112504Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190320T112504Z">
        <seg>•\quad Из DHT Kademlia извлекаются новые соседи-кандидаты.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\noindent</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.8em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>•\quad Obtain new candidates repeatedly, by looking up neighbor's neighbors.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190320T113032Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190320T113032Z">
        <seg>•\quad Периодически, отсмотром соседей соседей, получаются новые кандидаты.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\noindent</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.8em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>•\quad Probe and evaluate the transmission speed of each new candidate repeatedly, in a round robin fashion, rank the candidates based on the evaluation.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190320T113256Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190320T113256Z">
        <seg>•\quad Для каждого нового кандидата периодически замеряется и вычисляется скорость передачи, по принципу round-robin, кандидаты ранжируются по вычисленным значениям.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\noindent</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.6em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>•\quad Repeat the entire process.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190320T113729Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190320T113729Z">
        <seg>•\quad Весь процесс повторяется.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\noindent</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.8em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>•\quad Select candidates ranked at the top to replace eliminated neighbors.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190320T113717Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190320T113717Z">
        <seg>•\quad Для замены исключенных соседей, из головы отранжированного перечня, выбираются новые кандидаты.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\noindent</prop>
      <prop type="next">Subsequent segments and pieces from the current point of playback need to be prioritized in download scheduling, to maintain smooth streaming playback.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>•\quad Sequential download.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T103936Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T103936Z">
        <seg>•\quad Последовательное скачивание (Sequential download).</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\noindent</prop>
      <prop type="next">Newly joined nodes start with an empty list.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>•\quad Start by selecting an initial set of candidate neighbors among the peers with which it had connections in the past.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190320T112654Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190320T112249Z">
        <seg>•\quad Из пиров, с которыми имелось соединение в прошлом, формируется начальное множество соседей-кандидатов.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\noindent</prop>
      <prop type="next">Many media streaming applications allow random access playbacks such as fast forwarding or seeking.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>•\quad The anchor point.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T111342Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T105555Z">
        <seg>•\quad Опорная точка (The anchor point).</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\noindent</prop>
      <prop type="next">\vspace{-0.8em}</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>•\quad The world‘s only P2P data storage and transmission network that operates on more than 500 million nodes;</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T090144Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T090144Z">
        <seg>•\quad Единственная в мире одноранговая сеть хранения и передачи, функционирующая на более чем 500 миллионах узлах;</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\noindent</prop>
      <prop type="next">The unpopular pieces (especially in media streaming) need to be prioritized during download.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>•\quad Unpopular pieces.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T105225Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T105225Z">
        <seg>•\quad Непопулярные части (Unpopular pieces).</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\noindent</prop>
      <prop type="next">In the traditional Client-Server (CS) model, the server can quickly become the network bottleneck when the client population grows.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>•\quad {\bf  P2P Network:} PPIO constructs a self-governing, resilient and scalable P2P network that allows the participating nodes to easily share idle or unused bandwidth, storage, and computation resources.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190316T171900Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190316T171900Z">
        <seg>•\quad {\bf  Одноранговая сеть (P2P Network):} PPIO формирует самоорганизующуюся устойчивую и масштабируемую одноранговую (P2P) сеть, позволяющую участвующим в ней узлам легко совместно использовать простаивующую или не-используемую пропускную способность каналов связи, ресурсы хранилищ и вычислительные мощности.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\noindent</prop>
      <prop type="next">PPIO's consensus algorithm is designed by its use scenario.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>•\quad {\bf Consensus: } Popular blockchain consensus algorithms such as Proof of Work (PoW), Proof of Stake (PoS) and Delegated Proof of Stake (DPoS) all make trade-offs in decentralization, security and performance.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T084040Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T084040Z">
        <seg>•\quad {\bf Консенсус (Consensus): } Популярные алгоритмы консенсусов над блокчейнами, такие как Proof of Work (PoW), Proof of Stake (PoS) и Delegated Proof of Stake (DPoS) представляют собой компромисы между децентрализацией, безопасностью и быстродействием.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\noindent</prop>
      <prop type="next">By using data sharding and encryption algorithms, user's data can only be retrieved by the one who possesses the user's unique private key.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>•\quad {\bf Privacy, Security and Stability.} Data security and privacy protection are the top requirements in PPIO's distributed file system design.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190314T162928Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190314T162928Z">
        <seg>•\quad {\bf Приватность, безопасность и стабильность.} Безопасность и приватность данных являются ключевыми требованиями в дизайне распределенной файловой системе PPIO.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\noindent</prop>
      <prop type="next">PPIO incentives the nodes based on their contributions of storage and bandwidth, therefore the nodes incline to stay in the network and make a long and reliable contribution \cite{article1}.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>•\quad {\bf Proof:} The nodes of the traditional P2P network are free to choose join or leave the network, it is difficult to maintain the stability of the network.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190319T083329Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190319T082742Z">
        <seg>•\quad {\bf Доказательство (Proof):} Узлы традиционной P2P сети свободно присоединяются к сети и свободно покидают ее, в таких условиях сложно поддерживать стабильность сети.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\noindent</prop>
      <prop type="next">Besides a set of industry proven P2P transmission technologies, the team also developed data-driven scheduling, a self-organizing overlay network, and optimized content distribution network.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>•\quad {\bf Scalability and High Efficiency.} Benefit from the founding team's experience from creating and operating the distributed network with hundreds of millions of users, PPIO is designed from the ground up to perform efficiently at a global scale.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190314T161155Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190314T161155Z">
        <seg>•\quad {\bf Масштабируемость и высокая эффективность.} За счет опыта команды, извлеченного из создания и работы с распределенной сетью с тысячами миллионов пользователей, PPIO спроектирована с нуля до состояния, в котором она может быть эффективной в глобальном масштабе.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <prop type="file">WhitePaper_EN-1.tex</prop>
      <prop type="prev">\noindent</prop>
      <prop type="next">PPIO also has a set of technologies built into better support decentralized applications, including object-based storage, dApp Sandbox mechanisms, and file access management, etc.</prop>
      <tuv lang="EN-US">
        <seg>•\quad {\bf Strong Application Support and Ecosystem.} PPIO provides a set of storage APIs similar to those of the cloud services such as AWS S3 and makes the data migration from those services much comfortable.</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="RU" changeid="vopl" changedate="20190314T165936Z" creationid="vopl" creationdate="20190314T164941Z">
        <seg>•\quad {\bf Надежная поддержка приложений и экосистема.} PPIO предоставляет несколько программных интерфейсов хранилищ (Storage APIs), похожих на таковые в облачных сервисах, например AWS S3, и позволяет комфортно мигрироать данные из этих сервисов.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
  </body>
</tmx>
